[
  {
    "id": 2001,
    "question": "crisis",
    "questionDetails": "Todo el mundo a quien preguntas está en crisis.",
    "answer": "crisis, meltdown, seizure",
    "answerDetails": "Everyone you ask says they’re in a crisis."
  },
  {
    "id": 2002,
    "question": "volviendo",
    "questionDetails": "Escuché hoy que estás volviendo con nosotros.",
    "answer": "returning, becoming, getting",
    "answerDetails": "I hear today that you are returning to us."
  },
  {
    "id": 2003,
    "question": "intentado",
    "questionDetails": "Mejores hombres que tú han intentado eso antes.",
    "answer": "tried, attempted, sought",
    "answerDetails": "Better men than you have tried that already."
  },
  {
    "id": 2004,
    "question": "ponerte",
    "questionDetails": "Deberías ponerte mi ropa siempre.",
    "answer": "wear, get",
    "answerDetails": "You should always wear my clothes."
  },
  {
    "id": 2005,
    "question": "sensación",
    "questionDetails": "La sensación del agua contra su piel.",
    "answer": "feeling, sense, sensation",
    "answerDetails": "The feeling of the water against your skin."
  },
  {
    "id": 2006,
    "question": "ambiente",
    "questionDetails": "El líquido se almacena por debajo de la temperatura ambiente.",
    "answer": "ambient, ambience, vibe",
    "answerDetails": "The liquid is stored at below ambient temperature."
  },
  {
    "id": 2007,
    "question": "llamaron",
    "questionDetails": "Lo llamaron, pero él no los oyó.",
    "answer": "they called",
    "answerDetails": "They called him, but he didn’t hear them."
  },
  {
    "id": 2008,
    "question": "súper",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes ser súper sin ellos.",
    "answer": "super",
    "answerDetails": "You can be super without them."
  },
  {
    "id": 2009,
    "question": "confío",
    "questionDetails": "Yo confío de mis ojos.",
    "answer": "trust, entrust",
    "answerDetails": "I trust my own eyes."
  },
  {
    "id": 2010,
    "question": "mandé",
    "questionDetails": "Te mandé un libro, querida.",
    "answer": "sent, mande, mailed",
    "answerDetails": "I sent you a book, hon."
  },
  {
    "id": 2011,
    "question": "misión",
    "questionDetails": "El avión no estaba en la base, sino en una misión, cuando se produjo el ataque.",
    "answer": "assignment",
    "answerDetails": "The aircraft was on assignment away from its base when the attack took place."
  },
  {
    "id": 2012,
    "question": "restaurante",
    "questionDetails": "Tuvimos que cerrar el restaurante.",
    "answer": "restaurant",
    "answerDetails": "We had to close the restaurant."
  },
  {
    "id": 2013,
    "question": "internet",
    "answer": "Internet, online, web"
  },
  {
    "id": 2014,
    "question": "decidió",
    "answer": "Decided"
  },
  {
    "id": 2015,
    "question": "lengua",
    "questionDetails": "Su madre se puso detrás de ella, dando la lengua: “él te tiene en el extremo de una cuerda, ese hombre!.",
    "answer": "tongue",
    "answerDetails": "Her mother stood behind her, giving tongue: ‘He’s got you on the end of a string, that fellow!’."
  },
  {
    "id": 2016,
    "question": "divertido",
    "questionDetails": "Estar en conjunto con el reparto y la tripulación fue muy divertido.",
    "answer": "fun, amusing, entertaining",
    "answerDetails": "Being on set with the cast and crew was really fun."
  },
  {
    "id": 2017,
    "question": "darles",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando me encuentro con méndigos en la calle, nunca sé si darles dinero o comida.",
    "answer": "give them",
    "answerDetails": "When I see beggars on the street, I never know whether to give them money or food."
  },
  {
    "id": 2018,
    "question": "luchar",
    "questionDetails": "Los 2 luchadores de sumo tienen que luchar hasta que uno saque al otro del círculo.",
    "answer": "wrestle",
    "answerDetails": "The sumo wrestlers have to wrestle until one man is pushed out of the circle."
  },
  {
    "id": 2019,
    "question": "defensa",
    "questionDetails": "La defensa está lista para traer su primer testigo.",
    "answer": "defense, defence",
    "answerDetails": "The defense is ready to bring its first witness."
  },
  {
    "id": 2020,
    "question": "espíritu",
    "questionDetails": "Puede ser muy sincero cuando el espíritu lo mueve.",
    "answer": "spirit",
    "answerDetails": "He can be quite candid when the spirit moves him."
  },
  {
    "id": 2021,
    "question": "sales",
    "questionDetails": "Un baño con sales es más relajante.",
    "answer": "salts",
    "answerDetails": "A bath with some salts is more relaxing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2022,
    "question": "pudimos",
    "questionDetails": "Hicimos lo que pudimos.",
    "answer": "could",
    "answerDetails": "We did what we could."
  },
  {
    "id": 2023,
    "question": "desaparecer",
    "questionDetails": "Le di tiempo para desaparecer.",
    "answer": "disappear",
    "answerDetails": "I gave her time to disappear."
  },
  {
    "id": 2024,
    "question": "ayudas",
    "questionDetails": "Ayudas para la contratación de personal especializado.",
    "answer": "aid, help, grants",
    "answerDetails": "Aid for the signing up of specialized personnel."
  },
  {
    "id": 2025,
    "question": "sociales",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestras asignaciones sociales van a quemarse.",
    "answer": "social",
    "answerDetails": "Our social expenditure is set to spiral."
  },
  {
    "id": 2026,
    "question": "versión",
    "questionDetails": "La versión de los acontecimientos de Marco no coincide con la de Gloria.",
    "answer": "version, rendering",
    "answerDetails": "Marco’s version of events does not match Gloria’s."
  },
  {
    "id": 2027,
    "question": "mismas",
    "questionDetails": "El peso y estatura son las mismas.",
    "answer": "same, themselves, thereof",
    "answerDetails": "Height and weight are about the same."
  },
  {
    "id": 2028,
    "question": "descubrir",
    "questionDetails": "Me levanto y me voy a la oficina, para descubrir que es domingo.",
    "answer": "discover",
    "answerDetails": "I get up and go to my office, only to discover that it is Sunday."
  },
  {
    "id": 2029,
    "question": "continuar",
    "questionDetails": "El ensayo clínico no continuará después de estos problemas.",
    "answer": "continue, proceed",
    "answerDetails": "The clinical trial will not continue after these problems."
  },
  {
    "id": 2030,
    "question": "cerebro",
    "questionDetails": "El cerebro es el órgano más importante del cuerpo.",
    "answer": "brain",
    "answerDetails": "The brain is the most important organ in the body."
  },
  {
    "id": 2031,
    "question": "plaza",
    "questionDetails": "Fueron a la plaza para comprar frutas frescas.",
    "answer": "market",
    "answerDetails": "They went to the market to buy fresh fruit."
  },
  {
    "id": 2032,
    "question": "pedazo",
    "questionDetails": "No pude acabarme la comida y dejé un pedazo de carne en el plato.",
    "answer": "piece, chunk",
    "answerDetails": "I couldn’t finish my meal and I left a piece of meat on the plate."
  },
  {
    "id": 2033,
    "question": "sacando",
    "questionDetails": "Están sacando la alfombra según hablamos.",
    "answer": "pulling, taking, scooping",
    "answerDetails": "They are pulling the rug as we speak."
  },
  {
    "id": 2034,
    "question": "regaló",
    "questionDetails": "Me lo regaló él.",
    "answer": "gave, gifted",
    "answerDetails": "He gave it to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2035,
    "question": "mataron",
    "questionDetails": "Los rebeldes asaltaron los pueblos y mataron a mujeres y niños de manera indiscriminada.",
    "answer": "they killed, they were killed",
    "answerDetails": "The rebels stormed villages and they killed women and children indiscriminately."
  },
  {
    "id": 2036,
    "question": "club",
    "questionDetails": "Vamos a ir a un nuevo club del centro.",
    "answer": "club",
    "answerDetails": "Some of us are going downtown to a new club."
  },
  {
    "id": 2037,
    "question": "modelo",
    "questionDetails": "Modelos de cera fueron utilizados por los escultores en el método de cera perdida de fundición de bronce.",
    "answer": "model, design, pattern",
    "answerDetails": "Wax models were used by sculptors in the lost wax method of bronze casting."
  },
  {
    "id": 2038,
    "question": "pienses",
    "questionDetails": "No pienses en nada más.",
    "answer": "think",
    "answerDetails": "Think of nothing else."
  },
  {
    "id": 2039,
    "question": "cobarde",
    "questionDetails": "Un farsante, mentiroso y cobarde.",
    "answer": "coward",
    "answerDetails": "A fake, he’s a liar and a coward."
  },
  {
    "id": 2040,
    "question": "campeón",
    "questionDetails": "Su campeón es franco en su propósito.",
    "answer": "champion",
    "answerDetails": "Your champion is bold to his purpose."
  },
  {
    "id": 2041,
    "question": "jesús",
    "answer": "Jesus"
  },
  {
    "id": 2042,
    "question": "secretos",
    "questionDetails": "Mis secretos están seguros con ella.",
    "answer": "secrets",
    "answerDetails": "My secrets are safe with her."
  },
  {
    "id": 2043,
    "question": "seamos",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que seamos amigos de nuevo.",
    "answer": "be",
    "answerDetails": "I want to be friends again."
  },
  {
    "id": 2044,
    "question": "conseguí",
    "answer": "Got"
  },
  {
    "id": 2045,
    "question": "mías",
    "questionDetails": "Las trampas de abajo son mías.",
    "answer": "mine",
    "answerDetails": "Traps down there are mine."
  },
  {
    "id": 2046,
    "question": "carácter",
    "questionDetails": "Su arrebato estaba enteramente en el carácter.",
    "answer": "character",
    "answerDetails": "His outburst was entirely in character."
  },
  {
    "id": 2047,
    "question": "iguales",
    "questionDetails": "No todos los hombres son creados iguales.",
    "answer": "equal, alike, same",
    "answerDetails": "All men are not created equal."
  },
  {
    "id": 2048,
    "question": "fiestas",
    "questionDetails": "¿Se van a algún lado para las fiestas?",
    "answer": "holidays, holiday season",
    "answerDetails": "Are you going anywhere for the holidays?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2049,
    "question": "tontería",
    "questionDetails": "Valerie alegró nuestro ánimo sombrío con su tontería.",
    "answer": "silliness",
    "answerDetails": "Valerie brightened up our somber mood with her silliness."
  },
  {
    "id": 2050,
    "question": "respirar",
    "questionDetails": "Deje que su césped respirar por poner aire en el suelo.",
    "answer": "breathe",
    "answerDetails": "Let your lawn breathe by putting air into the soil."
  },
  {
    "id": 2051,
    "question": "cumple",
    "questionDetails": "Cumple una condena de 6 años en una cárcel estatal.",
    "answer": "he serves",
    "answerDetails": "He serves a 6-year sentence in a state prison."
  },
  {
    "id": 2052,
    "question": "pagado",
    "questionDetails": "Había pagado un precio muy alto.",
    "answer": "paid",
    "answerDetails": "I paid too high a price."
  },
  {
    "id": 2053,
    "question": "fumar",
    "questionDetails": "Fumar está prohibido en lugares públicos cerrados.",
    "answer": "smoking, smoke",
    "answerDetails": "Smoking is prohibited in closed public spaces."
  },
  {
    "id": 2054,
    "question": "pedro",
    "questionDetails": "Pedro se fue a la playa para pescar.",
    "answer": "peter",
    "answerDetails": "Peter went to the beach to go fishing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2055,
    "question": "gloria",
    "questionDetails": "El barco fue soplado a la gloria.",
    "answer": "glory",
    "answerDetails": "The boat was blown to glory."
  },
  {
    "id": 2056,
    "question": "primo",
    "questionDetails": "Primo (a) Hermano (a).",
    "answer": "cousin",
    "answerDetails": "First cousin."
  },
  {
    "id": 2057,
    "question": "entrevista",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que la entrevista ha terminado.",
    "answer": "interview",
    "answerDetails": "I guess the interview’s over."
  },
  {
    "id": 2058,
    "question": "entere",
    "questionDetails": "Ya verás cuando se entere de mi regalo de bodas.",
    "answer": "hears, learns, know",
    "answerDetails": "Wait till he hears about my wedding present."
  },
  {
    "id": 2059,
    "question": "sufrir",
    "questionDetails": "y otras palabras y definiciones pueden sufrir cambios",
    "answer": "undergo",
    "answerDetails": "and other words and definitions may undergo changes"
  },
  {
    "id": 2060,
    "question": "hablaste",
    "questionDetails": "Hablaste con tu tía sobre lo del carro, ¿no?",
    "answer": "you talked",
    "answerDetails": "You talked to your aunt about the car, right?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2061,
    "question": "andaba",
    "questionDetails": "Papá nunca andaba cerca.",
    "answer": "was",
    "answerDetails": "Dad was never around."
  },
  {
    "id": 2062,
    "question": "baile",
    "questionDetails": "El príncipe la invitó al baile.",
    "answer": "ball",
    "answerDetails": "The prince invited her to the ball."
  },
  {
    "id": 2063,
    "question": "explicación",
    "questionDetails": "Se marchó sin ninguna explicación.",
    "answer": "explanation",
    "answerDetails": "She left without an explanation."
  },
  {
    "id": 2064,
    "question": "agarra",
    "questionDetails": "Agarra el otro extremo de esto.",
    "answer": "grab",
    "answerDetails": "Grab the other end of this."
  },
  {
    "id": 2065,
    "question": "buscarlo",
    "questionDetails": "No tengo el número de teléfono del Mecánico. ¿Puedes buscarlo?",
    "answer": "look it up",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t know the mechanic’s phone number. Can you look it up?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2066,
    "question": "ponerse",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo hay que ponerse en esa postura.",
    "answer": "get",
    "answerDetails": "You only have to get in that position."
  },
  {
    "id": 2067,
    "question": "punta",
    "questionDetails": "Él me enseñó la punta de su lengua.",
    "answer": "tip, rush, peak",
    "answerDetails": "He showed me the tip of his tongue."
  },
  {
    "id": 2068,
    "question": "internacional",
    "questionDetails": "Derecho internacional.",
    "answer": "international",
    "answerDetails": "International law."
  },
  {
    "id": 2069,
    "question": "libros",
    "questionDetails": "Disfruten juntos de los libros con rimas.",
    "answer": "books, textbooks, workbooks",
    "answerDetails": "Enjoy rhyming books together."
  },
  {
    "id": 2070,
    "question": "existen",
    "questionDetails": "Pero existen hipótesis que compiten también.",
    "answer": "exist",
    "answerDetails": "But competing hypotheses exist as well."
  },
  {
    "id": 2071,
    "question": "corriente",
    "questionDetails": "Será más difícil ir en canoa al norte porque estaremos remando contra la corriente.",
    "answer": "stream, running, flow",
    "answerDetails": "It will be more difficult to canoe north because we’ll be rowing against the stream."
  },
  {
    "id": 2072,
    "question": "uso",
    "questionDetails": "El pintor siguió el uso religioso y costumbre de su tiempo.",
    "answer": "use, usage, application",
    "answerDetails": "The painter followed the religious use and wont of his time."
  },
  {
    "id": 2073,
    "question": "serás",
    "questionDetails": "Natalia, ¿serás mi esposa?",
    "answer": "will you be",
    "answerDetails": "Natalia, will you be my wife?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2074,
    "question": "pegado",
    "questionDetails": "Todos los imanes estaban pegados al lado de la nevera.",
    "answer": "stuck",
    "answerDetails": "All of the magnets were stuck to the side of the fridge."
  },
  {
    "id": 2075,
    "question": "figura",
    "questionDetails": "Tener buena figura.",
    "answer": "figure",
    "answerDetails": "To have a good figure."
  },
  {
    "id": 2076,
    "question": "naturaleza",
    "questionDetails": "Es en la naturaleza de las cosas que la mayoría de los premios de música se establecen para los artistas intérpretes en lugar de compositores.",
    "answer": "nature, wild",
    "answerDetails": "It is in the nature of things that the majority of music prizes get set up for performers rather than composers."
  },
  {
    "id": 2077,
    "question": "sentado",
    "questionDetails": "Estabas sentado en la silla cuando te dormiste.",
    "answer": "seated",
    "answerDetails": "You were seated in the chair when you fell asleep."
  },
  {
    "id": 2078,
    "question": "blanca",
    "questionDetails": "Trajimos algo de arena blanca.",
    "answer": "white",
    "answerDetails": "We got us some white sand."
  },
  {
    "id": 2079,
    "question": "chiquita",
    "answer": "Chiquita, little girl"
  },
  {
    "id": 2080,
    "question": "operación",
    "questionDetails": "Es una operación legítima.",
    "answer": "operation",
    "answerDetails": "This is a legitimate operation, okay?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2081,
    "question": "informe",
    "questionDetails": "La tesorera le dio su informe de presupuesto al comité.",
    "answer": "report",
    "answerDetails": "The treasurer gave her budget report to the committee."
  },
  {
    "id": 2082,
    "question": "pista",
    "questionDetails": "Los perros solo pudieron seguir su pista hasta la frontera con México.",
    "answer": "track, court, runway",
    "answerDetails": "Their dogs could follow the track only as far as the Mexican border."
  },
  {
    "id": 2083,
    "question": "ando",
    "answer": "Ando"
  },
  {
    "id": 2084,
    "question": "pistola",
    "questionDetails": "El hombre guardó la pistola en un cajón con llave.",
    "answer": "gun, pistol",
    "answerDetails": "The man put his gun away in a locked drawer."
  },
  {
    "id": 2085,
    "question": "mercado",
    "questionDetails": "El mercado del Reino Unido permaneció en recesión.",
    "answer": "market",
    "answerDetails": "The UK market remained in recession."
  },
  {
    "id": 2086,
    "question": "imaginas",
    "questionDetails": "Puedo saber que imaginas.",
    "answer": "imagine",
    "answerDetails": "I can hardly see what you imagine."
  },
  {
    "id": 2087,
    "question": "condición",
    "questionDetails": "Sorprendentemente, estar casado era una condición obligatoria para solicitar el puesto.",
    "answer": "condition",
    "answerDetails": "Surprisingly, being married was a mandatory condition to apply for the job."
  },
  {
    "id": 2088,
    "question": "cine",
    "questionDetails": "Escribe artículos sobre cine y literatura para el periódico local.",
    "answer": "film, cinema, movies",
    "answerDetails": "He writes articles on film and literature for the local Paper."
  },
  {
    "id": 2089,
    "question": "humor",
    "questionDetails": "El profesor estaba de buen humor y no tenemos deberes para hoy.",
    "answer": "mood, humour",
    "answerDetails": "The teacher was in a good mood, and we have no homework for today."
  },
  {
    "id": 2090,
    "question": "denuncia",
    "questionDetails": "Rafael llamó a la policía para registrar una denuncia contra sus vecinos escandalosos.",
    "answer": "complaint",
    "answerDetails": "Rafael called the police to make a complaint against his noisy neighbors."
  },
  {
    "id": 2091,
    "question": "veremos",
    "questionDetails": "Veremos un cortometraje sobre la vida en Perú y después comentaremos su contenido.",
    "answer": "we will watch",
    "answerDetails": "We will watch a short movie about life in Peru and then we will comment on its content."
  },
  {
    "id": 2092,
    "question": "calidad",
    "questionDetails": "Calidad de vida.",
    "answer": "quality",
    "answerDetails": "Quality of life."
  },
  {
    "id": 2093,
    "question": "supiera",
    "questionDetails": "Ojalá yo lo supiera.",
    "answer": "knew",
    "answerDetails": "I wish i knew."
  },
  {
    "id": 2094,
    "question": "temas",
    "questionDetails": "Si supiera qué temas van a salir.",
    "answer": "topics, themes, issues",
    "answerDetails": "I wonder what topics will come up."
  },
  {
    "id": 2095,
    "question": "gratis",
    "questionDetails": "La mantuve fuera del viento y navegando gratis hasta que tenía todo cuadrado hacia adelante.",
    "answer": "free",
    "answerDetails": "I kept her off the wind and sailing free until I had all square forward."
  },
  {
    "id": 2096,
    "question": "quedaste",
    "questionDetails": "Pero tú te quedaste y no pasó nada.",
    "answer": "stayed",
    "answerDetails": "But you stayed on and nothing happened."
  },
  {
    "id": 2097,
    "question": "pobres",
    "questionDetails": "La brecha entre los ricos y los pobres se ha ampliado.",
    "answer": "poor",
    "answerDetails": "The gap between the rich and the poor has widened."
  },
  {
    "id": 2098,
    "question": "pasos",
    "questionDetails": "El padre de Vicente fue barbero antes que él, y ahora le sigue los pasos.",
    "answer": "footsteps",
    "answerDetails": "Vicente’s father was a barber before him, and now he’s following in his footsteps."
  },
  {
    "id": 2099,
    "question": "serie",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuál es tu serie preferida en este momento?",
    "answer": "series, serial",
    "answerDetails": "What’s your favorite series right now?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2100,
    "question": "excusa",
    "questionDetails": "Pero sigue sin ser una excusa.",
    "answer": "excuse",
    "answerDetails": "But that’s still no excuse."
  },
  {
    "id": 2101,
    "question": "especialmente",
    "questionDetails": "Escrito especialmente para Jonathan.",
    "answer": "especially, particularly, specifically",
    "answerDetails": "Written especially for Jonathan."
  },
  {
    "id": 2102,
    "question": "termino",
    "questionDetails": "Ese termino casi siempre es mal empleado.",
    "answer": "term, ended up",
    "answerDetails": "That term is almost always misused."
  },
  {
    "id": 2103,
    "question": "claramente",
    "questionDetails": "Oí claramente a tu suegra describirte como una serpiente.",
    "answer": "distinctly, plainly",
    "answerDetails": "I distinctly heard your mother-in-law describe you as a snake."
  },
  {
    "id": 2104,
    "question": "quienes",
    "questionDetails": "Estas son las personas con quienes te has estado comunicando por correo electrónico.",
    "answer": "whom",
    "answerDetails": "These are the people with whom you’ve been communicating via email."
  },
  {
    "id": 2105,
    "question": "pierna",
    "questionDetails": "Me duelen las piernas después de tanto ejercicio.",
    "answer": "leg",
    "answerDetails": "My legs hurt after all that exercise."
  },
  {
    "id": 2106,
    "question": "mayores",
    "questionDetails": "No cuando las partes son mayores.",
    "answer": "elderly",
    "answerDetails": "Not when the parties are elderly."
  },
  {
    "id": 2107,
    "question": "chao",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Chao! Nos vemos mañana.",
    "answer": "ciao, bye",
    "answerDetails": "Ciao! I’ll see you tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "id": 2108,
    "question": "madres",
    "questionDetails": "Y las madres que han perdido hijos.",
    "answer": "mothers, moms, mums",
    "answerDetails": "And mothers who lost sons."
  },
  {
    "id": 2109,
    "question": "alegra",
    "questionDetails": "Me alegra estemos de acuerdo.",
    "answer": "am glad, glad, am pleased",
    "answerDetails": "I am glad we agreed to it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2110,
    "question": "sombra",
    "questionDetails": "Su nuevo cachorro es su sombra. A dónde vaya ella, va él.",
    "answer": "shadow, shade",
    "answerDetails": "Her new puppy is her shadow. He goes wherever she does."
  },
  {
    "id": 2111,
    "question": "convencer",
    "questionDetails": "Tuvimos que convencer a los políticos de que necesitaban hacer algo.",
    "answer": "convince, persuade",
    "answerDetails": "We had to convince politicians that they needed to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 2112,
    "question": "carga",
    "questionDetails": "No Desenchufe el cargador hasta que la carga haya finalizado.",
    "answer": "load, charge, burden",
    "answerDetails": "Don’t remove the charger until the load is complete."
  },
  {
    "id": 2113,
    "question": "costa",
    "questionDetails": "Pasamos la Navidad en la costa de Chile y disfrutamos del clima veraniego.",
    "answer": "coast, shore, seaside",
    "answerDetails": "We spent Christmas on the coast of Chile and enjoyed the summer weather."
  },
  {
    "id": 2114,
    "question": "robó",
    "questionDetails": "Ella robó el libro.",
    "answer": "stole, robbed",
    "answerDetails": "She stole the ledger."
  },
  {
    "id": 2115,
    "question": "reglas",
    "questionDetails": "Tres reglas de éxito, la manera de educación completa.",
    "answer": "rules, regulations, ruling",
    "answerDetails": "Three rules of success, the way of complete education."
  },
  {
    "id": 2116,
    "question": "pertenece",
    "questionDetails": "Y la tuya me pertenece a mí.",
    "answer": "belongs, pertains, owned",
    "answerDetails": "And yours belongs to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2117,
    "question": "olvídate",
    "questionDetails": "Olvídate que estás aquí.",
    "answer": "forget",
    "answerDetails": "Forget that you are even here."
  },
  {
    "id": 2118,
    "question": "local",
    "questionDetails": "Compré la licuadora por Internet y mañana pasaré por el local a retirarla.",
    "answer": "store, premises",
    "answerDetails": "I bought the blender online and will pick it up from the store tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "id": 2119,
    "question": "maravillosa",
    "questionDetails": "Es una planta realmente maravillosa.",
    "answer": "wonderful, marvelous, wondrous",
    "answerDetails": "It is a really wonderful plant."
  },
  {
    "id": 2120,
    "question": "compra",
    "questionDetails": "Las pezuñas del caballo lucharon por la compra en el pavimento resbaladizo.",
    "answer": "purchase, purchasing",
    "answerDetails": "The horse’s hooves fought for purchase on the slippery pavement."
  },
  {
    "id": 2121,
    "question": "detener",
    "questionDetails": "Estudiantes universitarios de la comunidad son más propensos a detenerse, o abandonar por completo, cuando el costo de asistir a aumentos.",
    "answer": "stop, stem",
    "answerDetails": "Community college students are more likely to stop out, or drop out entirely, when the cost of attending increases."
  },
  {
    "id": 2122,
    "question": "terminé",
    "questionDetails": "Me senté a descansar un rato y terminé durmiendo aquí.",
    "answer": "ended up, finished",
    "answerDetails": "I just sat around for a while and ended up crashing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2123,
    "question": "saludar",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo que ir a saludar a mi amigo.",
    "answer": "say hello",
    "answerDetails": "I have to go say hello to a friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 2124,
    "question": "limpia",
    "questionDetails": "Limpia esto por mi.",
    "answer": "clean, cleanses, wipe",
    "answerDetails": "Clean this off for me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2125,
    "question": "últimas",
    "questionDetails": "Las últimas obras de arte de mi hijo.",
    "answer": "latest, last, past",
    "answerDetails": "The latest masterpieces from my son."
  },
  {
    "id": 2126,
    "question": "pases",
    "questionDetails": "Hice once pases consecutivos.",
    "answer": "passes, passing",
    "answerDetails": "I made eleven passes in a row."
  },
  {
    "id": 2127,
    "question": "parecido",
    "questionDetails": "Tu coche es parecido al mío.",
    "answer": "similar, resemblance, akin",
    "answerDetails": "Your car is similar to mine."
  },
  {
    "id": 2128,
    "question": "llames",
    "questionDetails": "Si te metes en líos no me llames.",
    "answer": "call",
    "answerDetails": "If you get in trouble, don’t call me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2129,
    "question": "prohibido",
    "questionDetails": "Nadie ha prohibido entrenar todavía.",
    "answer": "banned",
    "answerDetails": "No one’s banned exercising yet."
  },
  {
    "id": 2130,
    "question": "ma",
    "questionDetails": "Ma dice que usted no es muy bien.",
    "answer": "ma",
    "answerDetails": "Ma says you’re not very well."
  },
  {
    "id": 2131,
    "question": "aeropuerto",
    "questionDetails": "No puede salir del aeropuerto.",
    "answer": "airport",
    "answerDetails": "He can´t get out of the airport."
  },
  {
    "id": 2132,
    "question": "proteger",
    "questionDetails": "El nuevo sistema de alarmas protegerá mejor el edificio.",
    "answer": "secure, safeguard",
    "answerDetails": "Our new alarm system will better secure the building."
  },
  {
    "id": 2133,
    "question": "responder",
    "questionDetails": "Espera a que yo te llame antes de responder a mi pregunta.",
    "answer": "respond, answer, reply",
    "answerDetails": "Wait until I call your name before you respond to my question."
  },
  {
    "id": 2134,
    "question": "testigo",
    "questionDetails": "El jurado toma la decisión, no el testigo.",
    "answer": "witness",
    "answerDetails": "The jury makes that determination, not the witness."
  },
  {
    "id": 2135,
    "question": "oyes",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que me oyes.",
    "answer": "hear",
    "answerDetails": "I know you hear me!"
  },
  {
    "id": 2136,
    "question": "saque",
    "answer": "serve"
  },
  {
    "id": 2137,
    "question": "encerrado",
    "questionDetails": "Me siento encerrado en este lugar.",
    "answer": "cooped up",
    "answerDetails": "I feel so cooped up in this place."
  },
  {
    "id": 2138,
    "question": "tonterías",
    "questionDetails": "No me creo esas tonterías de que la casa está embrujada.",
    "answer": "nonsense, baloney, rubbish",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t believe in all this nonsense about the house being haunted."
  },
  {
    "id": 2139,
    "question": "nervios",
    "questionDetails": "Mi madre es obsesiva y padece de los nervios.",
    "answer": "nerves",
    "answerDetails": "My mother is obsessive and suffers from nerves."
  },
  {
    "id": 2140,
    "question": "familiares",
    "questionDetails": "Los familiares de Arkansas de Tonya la visitaron para Navidad en California.",
    "answer": "kin",
    "answerDetails": "Tonya’s Kin from Arkansas visited her in California at Christmas."
  },
  {
    "id": 2141,
    "question": "señoras",
    "questionDetails": "Señoras, cometen un gran error.",
    "answer": "ladies, Madams",
    "answerDetails": "You ladies are making a big mistake."
  },
  {
    "id": 2142,
    "question": "declaración",
    "questionDetails": "Aún no se ha emitido una declaración de guerra, no obstante, el Presidente ha enviado Tropas.",
    "answer": "declaration",
    "answerDetails": "A declaration of war has not been issued yet; nonetheless, the President has sent troops."
  },
  {
    "id": 2143,
    "question": "dijera",
    "questionDetails": "Alguien que hiciera lo que se le dijera.",
    "answer": "told",
    "answerDetails": "Someone who would do as they were told."
  },
  {
    "id": 2144,
    "question": "entrando",
    "questionDetails": "Entrando profundo en su sentido.",
    "answer": "entering, incoming",
    "answerDetails": "Entering deep in its sense."
  },
  {
    "id": 2145,
    "question": "acabe",
    "questionDetails": "Deja que acabe lo que empezó.",
    "answer": "finish",
    "answerDetails": "Let him finish what he started."
  },
  {
    "id": 2146,
    "question": "muera",
    "questionDetails": "Si tan sólo pudiera vivir aquí hasta que muera.",
    "answer": "die",
    "answerDetails": "If only we can live here till we die."
  },
  {
    "id": 2147,
    "question": "peores",
    "questionDetails": "Las primeras semanas son las peores.",
    "answer": "worst",
    "answerDetails": "The first two weeks are the worst."
  },
  {
    "id": 2148,
    "question": "desgracia",
    "questionDetails": "El proyecto fue perseguido por la desgracia.",
    "answer": "misfortune",
    "answerDetails": "The project was dogged by misfortune."
  },
  {
    "id": 2149,
    "question": "intenté",
    "questionDetails": "En realidad nunca lo intenté.",
    "answer": "tried",
    "answerDetails": "Never actually tried that."
  },
  {
    "id": 2150,
    "question": "falso",
    "questionDetails": "Eso es totalmente falso.",
    "answer": "untrue",
    "answerDetails": "That is completely untrue."
  },
  {
    "id": 2151,
    "question": "tendrías",
    "questionDetails": "Me lo tendrías que haber dicho.",
    "answer": "have",
    "answerDetails": "I got him to have said."
  },
  {
    "id": 2152,
    "question": "robado",
    "questionDetails": "Los policías arrestaron a los hombres que escondían el cuadro robado.",
    "answer": "robbed",
    "answerDetails": "The policemen arrested the men who were hiding the robbed painting."
  },
  {
    "id": 2153,
    "question": "echa",
    "questionDetails": "Echa un vistazo a la herida de entrada.",
    "answer": "take, misses, throws",
    "answerDetails": "Take a look at the entry wound."
  },
  {
    "id": 2154,
    "question": "vives",
    "questionDetails": "¿Vives en la zona?-No. Solo trabajo aquí.",
    "answer": "do you live",
    "answerDetails": "Do you live in the area?-No, I don’t. I just work here."
  },
  {
    "id": 2155,
    "question": "gato",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo que cambiar un neumático pinchado y el gato está roto.",
    "answer": "jack",
    "answerDetails": "I need to change a flat tire, and the Jack is broken."
  },
  {
    "id": 2156,
    "question": "trago",
    "questionDetails": "Solo necesita un trago para dejarlo inconsciente el resto de la noche.",
    "answer": "drink, swig, gulp",
    "answerDetails": "It only takes one drink to knock him out for the night."
  },
  {
    "id": 2157,
    "question": "enteré",
    "questionDetails": "Me enteré de que querías venir a visitarme al hospital.",
    "answer": "heard, learned",
    "answerDetails": "I heard you wanted to visit me at the hospital."
  },
  {
    "id": 2158,
    "question": "cartas",
    "questionDetails": "Pero vieron las cartas que le enviaste.",
    "answer": "letters, cards, charts",
    "answerDetails": "They took the letters you sent her."
  },
  {
    "id": 2159,
    "question": "virgen",
    "questionDetails": "Él es una Virgen política.",
    "answer": "virgin, madonna",
    "answerDetails": "He’s a political virgin."
  },
  {
    "id": 2160,
    "question": "entendiendo",
    "questionDetails": "Tu no estás entendiendo algo.",
    "answer": "understanding",
    "answerDetails": "You are not understanding something."
  },
  {
    "id": 2161,
    "question": "abra",
    "questionDetails": "Abra el documento que desee previsualizar.",
    "answer": "open, unlock",
    "answerDetails": "Open the document you want to preview."
  },
  {
    "id": 2162,
    "question": "deuda",
    "questionDetails": "Una manera de reducir la deuda del Tercer Mundo.",
    "answer": "debt",
    "answerDetails": "A way to reduce Third World debt."
  },
  {
    "id": 2163,
    "question": "camión",
    "questionDetails": "El camión llegó tarde.",
    "answer": "bus, rig",
    "answerDetails": "The bus arrived late."
  },
  {
    "id": 2164,
    "question": "pare",
    "questionDetails": "Pare y abra la puerta.",
    "answer": "stop, calves",
    "answerDetails": "Stop and open the door."
  },
  {
    "id": 2165,
    "question": "salvo",
    "questionDetails": "Todos los rehenes fueron rescatados sanos y salvos.",
    "answer": "safe, except, save",
    "answerDetails": "All the Hostages were rescued safe and sound."
  },
  {
    "id": 2166,
    "question": "arreglo",
    "questionDetails": "Ángel hizo que llevaran un arreglo floral a la oficina de su esposa.",
    "answer": "arrangement, fix",
    "answerDetails": "Angel had a flower arrangement delivered to his wife’s office."
  },
  {
    "id": 2167,
    "question": "silla",
    "questionDetails": "¿Esta silla está ocupada?",
    "answer": "seat, saddle",
    "answerDetails": "Is this seat taken?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2168,
    "question": "detenido",
    "questionDetails": "Los adolescentes detenidos no sabían que tenían el derecho de llamar a un abogado.",
    "answer": "arrested, detainee",
    "answerDetails": "The arrested teenagers didn’t know they were entitled to call a lawyer."
  },
  {
    "id": 2169,
    "question": "encuentre",
    "questionDetails": "Quizá lo encuentre un niño.",
    "answer": "find, locate, encounter",
    "answerDetails": "Some kid might find that."
  },
  {
    "id": 2170,
    "question": "hogar",
    "questionDetails": "Bienvenidos a nuestro hogar. Por favor, pónganse cómodos.",
    "answer": "home, household, hearth",
    "answerDetails": "Welcome to our home. Please, make yourselves comfortable."
  },
  {
    "id": 2171,
    "question": "pieza",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quieres una pieza de fruta?",
    "answer": "piece",
    "answerDetails": "Would you like a piece of fruit?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2172,
    "question": "millón",
    "answer": "billion"
  },
  {
    "id": 2173,
    "question": "comenzar",
    "questionDetails": "Me gusta comenzar el día con una taza de café caliente.",
    "answer": "begin, start, commence",
    "answerDetails": "I like to begin the day with a cup of hot coffee."
  },
  {
    "id": 2174,
    "question": "pesadilla",
    "questionDetails": "Cambiaría una pesadilla por otra.",
    "answer": "nightmare",
    "answerDetails": "Just trade one nightmare for another."
  },
  {
    "id": 2175,
    "question": "controlar",
    "questionDetails": "Las cosas se pueden controlar.",
    "answer": "control",
    "answerDetails": "You can control things."
  },
  {
    "id": 2176,
    "question": "devolver",
    "questionDetails": "Restar, devolver el servicio.",
    "answer": "return, refund",
    "answerDetails": "To return service."
  },
  {
    "id": 2177,
    "question": "pasión",
    "questionDetails": "La pasión de sus primeros años juntos se fue apagando con el tiempo.",
    "answer": "passion",
    "answerDetails": "The passion of their first years together faded with time."
  },
  {
    "id": 2178,
    "question": "coge",
    "questionDetails": "Pero si te coge mintiendo .",
    "answer": "catches, take, grab",
    "answerDetails": "But if he catches someone lying."
  },
  {
    "id": 2179,
    "question": "gritar",
    "questionDetails": "Gritarle algo a alguien.",
    "answer": "shout, holler, bawl",
    "answerDetails": "To shout something at somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 2180,
    "question": "crecer",
    "questionDetails": "Él vería a Nick crecer a la virilidad.",
    "answer": "grow",
    "answerDetails": "He would watch Nick grow to manhood."
  },
  {
    "id": 2181,
    "question": "opciones",
    "questionDetails": "Incluye opciones de espejado sincrónico y asincrónico.",
    "answer": "options, choices, settings",
    "answerDetails": "Includes synchronous and asynchronous mirroring options."
  },
  {
    "id": 2182,
    "question": "humanos",
    "questionDetails": "Es el alma lo que nos hace humanos.",
    "answer": "human",
    "answerDetails": "It is the soul that makes us human."
  },
  {
    "id": 2183,
    "question": "dedos",
    "questionDetails": "Es la diferencia entre uno y tres dedos.",
    "answer": "fingers, toes, digits",
    "answerDetails": "The difference between two and three fingers."
  },
  {
    "id": 2184,
    "question": "efectivamente",
    "questionDetails": "Y, efectivamente, tiene un defecto.",
    "answer": "indeed",
    "answerDetails": "And indeed it has a flaw."
  },
  {
    "id": 2185,
    "question": "luces",
    "questionDetails": "Acabamos de montar nuestras luces navideñas, y se ven fantásticas.",
    "answer": "illuminations",
    "answerDetails": "We’ve just put up our Christmas illuminations, and they look fantastic."
  },
  {
    "id": 2186,
    "question": "costado",
    "questionDetails": "Una flecha enemiga perforó el costado izquierdo del soldado.",
    "answer": "flank",
    "answerDetails": "An enemy arrow pierced the soldier’s left flank."
  },
  {
    "id": 2187,
    "question": "podían",
    "questionDetails": "Todos corrían lo mejor que podían para estar seguros.",
    "answer": "could",
    "answerDetails": "Everyone ran for safety as best they could."
  },
  {
    "id": 2188,
    "question": "distintas",
    "answer": "Different"
  },
  {
    "id": 2189,
    "question": "patrón",
    "questionDetails": "Si su patrón está de acuerdo, use este manuscrito.",
    "answer": "employer",
    "answerDetails": "If your employer agrees, use this manuscript."
  },
  {
    "id": 2190,
    "question": "junta",
    "questionDetails": "La Asociación de Propietarios elegirá una junta nueva el próximo lunes.",
    "answer": "board, meeting, joint",
    "answerDetails": "The homeowners’ association will elect a new board next Monday."
  },
  {
    "id": 2191,
    "question": "juicio",
    "questionDetails": "Fiarse (del juicio) de alguien.",
    "answer": "judgment, opinion, prosecution",
    "answerDetails": "To trust somebody’s judgment."
  },
  {
    "id": 2192,
    "question": "maldito",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Maldito! ¡ Lo olvidé por completo!.",
    "answer": "damn, bloody, freaking",
    "answerDetails": "Damn! I completely forgot!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2193,
    "question": "cosita",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Mira esa cosita!-Órale. ¿Eso es perro o ratón?",
    "answer": "little thing",
    "answerDetails": "Look at that little thing!-Woah. Is that a dog or a rat?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2194,
    "question": "escándalo",
    "questionDetails": "Provocar or ocasionar un escándalo.",
    "answer": "scandal",
    "answerDetails": "To create or cause a scandal."
  },
  {
    "id": 2195,
    "question": "estúpida",
    "questionDetails": "Me siento muy estúpida.",
    "answer": "stupid",
    "answerDetails": "I feel really stupid now."
  },
  {
    "id": 2196,
    "question": "bomba",
    "questionDetails": "Primero tienes que reparar el neumático, y después inflarlo con la bomba.",
    "answer": "pump, bomb",
    "answerDetails": "First you need to repair the tire, and then you inflate it with the pump."
  },
  {
    "id": 2197,
    "question": "fútbol",
    "questionDetails": "Necesitas Espinilleras si vas a jugar al Fútbol.",
    "answer": "soccer",
    "answerDetails": "You need shin guards if you’re going to play soccer."
  },
  {
    "id": 2198,
    "question": "agradecer",
    "questionDetails": "Usted sólo tiene que agradecer por la difícil situación que está en.",
    "answer": "thank",
    "answerDetails": "You have only yourself to thank for the plight you are in."
  },
  {
    "id": 2199,
    "question": "derechos",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo derechos como ciudadana de este país.",
    "answer": "rights, duties",
    "answerDetails": "I have rights as a citizen of this country."
  },
  {
    "id": 2200,
    "question": "alcohol",
    "questionDetails": "Mientras se quema el alcohol, se calienta el líquido en la probeta.",
    "answer": "spirit",
    "answerDetails": "As the spirit burns, the liquid in the test tube gets hot."
  },
  {
    "id": 2201,
    "question": "carretera",
    "questionDetails": "Encontramos precios en la carretera desde £ 5.780 hasta £ 6.151.",
    "answer": "road, highway, route",
    "answerDetails": "We found on-the-road prices from £5,780 to £6,151."
  },
  {
    "id": 2202,
    "question": "discutir",
    "questionDetails": "Discutiremos más tarde lo de ir a esa fiesta sin mi permiso.",
    "answer": "discuss, argue, debate",
    "answerDetails": "We’ll discuss the fact that you went to the party without my permission later."
  },
  {
    "id": 2203,
    "question": "seguros",
    "questionDetails": "La compañía de seguros insiste.",
    "answer": "insurance, safe, sure",
    "answerDetails": "The insurance company insists."
  },
  {
    "id": 2204,
    "question": "herido",
    "questionDetails": "Fue herido y está hospitalizado.",
    "answer": "hurt",
    "answerDetails": "He was hurt and is in hospital."
  },
  {
    "id": 2205,
    "question": "apellido",
    "questionDetails": "Mi apellido el mismo que mi hermano.",
    "answer": "surname",
    "answerDetails": "And my surname is the same as my brother."
  },
  {
    "id": 2206,
    "question": "veamos",
    "questionDetails": "Veamos lo que dice.",
    "answer": "see",
    "answerDetails": "See what it says."
  },
  {
    "id": 2207,
    "question": "cien",
    "questionDetails": "Otras cien personas se quedaron en el andén.",
    "answer": "hundred",
    "answerDetails": "The other hundred people stayed on that platform."
  },
  {
    "id": 2208,
    "question": "tratado",
    "questionDetails": "En su apuro por firmar el Tratado, no se dieron cuenta de que no había ninguna cláusula que prohibiera el uso de armas nucleares.",
    "answer": "treaty",
    "answerDetails": "In their haste to sign the treaty, they failed to realize that there was no clause prohibiting the use of nuclear weapons."
  },
  {
    "id": 2209,
    "question": "médicos",
    "questionDetails": "Los médicos no deben subir al ring.",
    "answer": "doctors, medical, physicians",
    "answerDetails": "Doctors should stay out of the ring."
  },
  {
    "id": 2210,
    "question": "sacamos",
    "questionDetails": "Lo sacamos de una revista.",
    "answer": "we",
    "answerDetails": "We saw it in a magazine."
  },
  {
    "id": 2211,
    "question": "seguido",
    "questionDetails": "La fiesta consistirá en un concierto seguido de fuegos artificiales.",
    "answer": "followed by, straight on",
    "answerDetails": "The fiesta will consist of a concert followed by fireworks."
  },
  {
    "id": 2212,
    "question": "olvides",
    "questionDetails": "Mi socio silencioso no me olvides.",
    "answer": "forget",
    "answerDetails": "My silent partner would not forget me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2213,
    "question": "darnos",
    "questionDetails": "El profesor Langley dijo que no va a darnos tarea hoy.",
    "answer": "give us",
    "answerDetails": "Professor Langley said he’s not going to give us homework today."
  },
  {
    "id": 2214,
    "question": "diario",
    "questionDetails": "A diario.",
    "answer": "daily, diary, newspaper",
    "answerDetails": "On a daily basis."
  },
  {
    "id": 2215,
    "question": "b",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 2216,
    "question": "vaso",
    "questionDetails": "Los niños bebieron un vaso de leche antes de irse a la cama.",
    "answer": "glass, vessel, cup",
    "answerDetails": "The kids drank a glass of milk before going to bed."
  },
  {
    "id": 2217,
    "question": "pon",
    "questionDetails": "Pon eso en el coche.",
    "answer": "put",
    "answerDetails": "Put it in the car."
  },
  {
    "id": 2218,
    "question": "beber",
    "questionDetails": "No se permite beber en el camión.",
    "answer": "drinking",
    "answerDetails": "There’s no drinking on the bus."
  },
  {
    "id": 2219,
    "question": "impresionante",
    "questionDetails": "Una vista impresionante de las montañas.",
    "answer": "impressive, stunning, breathtaking",
    "answerDetails": "An impressive view of the mountains."
  },
  {
    "id": 2220,
    "question": "puestos",
    "questionDetails": "Podéis volver a vuestros puestos.",
    "answer": "posts, stalls, positions",
    "answerDetails": "Then you may report back to your posts."
  },
  {
    "id": 2221,
    "question": "empezaron",
    "questionDetails": "Los niños empezaron a burlarse de ella.",
    "answer": "started, began",
    "answerDetails": "The kids have started teasing her."
  },
  {
    "id": 2222,
    "question": "anterior",
    "questionDetails": "Admito que podría haber sido un poco anterior.",
    "answer": "previous, former, prior",
    "answerDetails": "I admit I may have been a bit previous."
  },
  {
    "id": 2223,
    "question": "duerme",
    "questionDetails": "Duerme en paz celestial .",
    "answer": "sleep, asleep",
    "answerDetails": "Sleep in heavenly peace."
  },
  {
    "id": 2224,
    "question": "capitán",
    "questionDetails": "Yo soy su capitán.",
    "answer": "skipper",
    "answerDetails": "I am her skipper."
  },
  {
    "id": 2225,
    "question": "sr",
    "answer": "Mr"
  },
  {
    "id": 2226,
    "question": "negra",
    "questionDetails": "La gente negra nunca se convertiría en pilotos.",
    "answer": "black",
    "answerDetails": "Black people would never have become pilots."
  },
  {
    "id": 2227,
    "question": "profesor",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre que nosotros hablamos, el profesor grita.",
    "answer": "teacher",
    "answerDetails": "Whenever we spoke, the teacher screams."
  },
  {
    "id": 2228,
    "question": "diablo",
    "questionDetails": "Mi sobrino es un pequeño diablo.",
    "answer": "devil",
    "answerDetails": "My nephew is a little devil."
  },
  {
    "id": 2229,
    "question": "perdonar",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que Catherine me perdonará.",
    "answer": "pardon",
    "answerDetails": "I know Catherine will pardon me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2230,
    "question": "vinimos",
    "questionDetails": "Nadie respondió en la casa de Linda, así que vinimos a verte.",
    "answer": "we came",
    "answerDetails": "No one answered at Linda’s house, so we came to see you."
  },
  {
    "id": 2231,
    "question": "traen",
    "questionDetails": "El descanso y el ocio traen aburrimiento.",
    "answer": "bring",
    "answerDetails": "Rest and idleness bring boredom."
  },
  {
    "id": 2232,
    "question": "ánimo",
    "questionDetails": "Sus palabras de ánimo me ayudaron a salir de su depresión.",
    "answer": "encouragement, spirits, my heart",
    "answerDetails": "Her words of encouragement helped me to overcome her depression."
  },
  {
    "id": 2233,
    "question": "invitados",
    "questionDetails": "Los invitados llegarán en cualquier momento.",
    "answer": "guests, invited, invitees",
    "answerDetails": "We are expecting guests anytime."
  },
  {
    "id": 2234,
    "question": "chiquito",
    "questionDetails": "No es nada, chiquito.",
    "answer": "shorty, little boy, small",
    "answerDetails": "Ain’t no thing, shorty."
  },
  {
    "id": 2235,
    "question": "sucede",
    "questionDetails": "Es triste si le pasa a alguien más, pero si te sucede a tí, es trágico.",
    "answer": "it happens, it occurs, it takes place",
    "answerDetails": "It’s sad if it happens to someone else, but if it happens to you, it’s tragic."
  },
  {
    "id": 2236,
    "question": "guardar",
    "questionDetails": "Carolina decidió guardar su vestido nuevo para una ocasión especial.",
    "answer": "save, keep, store",
    "answerDetails": "Carolina decided to save her new dress for a special occasion."
  },
  {
    "id": 2237,
    "question": "corresponde",
    "questionDetails": "La túnica que llevamos se corresponde a una armadura.",
    "answer": "corresponds, applicable, belongs",
    "answerDetails": "The robe we wear corresponds to a suit of armor."
  },
  {
    "id": 2238,
    "question": "elegante",
    "questionDetails": "Una casa elegante y confortable.",
    "answer": "elegant, stylish, sleek",
    "answerDetails": "An elegant, comfortable house."
  },
  {
    "id": 2239,
    "question": "supo",
    "questionDetails": "Ella supo que era soltero porque no llevaba un anillo.",
    "answer": "she knew",
    "answerDetails": "She knew he was single because he wasn’t wearing a ring."
  },
  {
    "id": 2240,
    "question": "películas",
    "questionDetails": "Nos ocupamos tanto de hecho películas y televisión.",
    "answer": "films, movies, motion pictures",
    "answerDetails": "We deal with both actually films and tv."
  },
  {
    "id": 2241,
    "question": "canta",
    "answer": "Sings"
  },
  {
    "id": 2242,
    "question": "visitas",
    "questionDetails": "Las visitas parecen darte apetito.",
    "answer": "visits, tours, hits",
    "answerDetails": "Visits seem to give you an appetite."
  },
  {
    "id": 2243,
    "question": "tendré",
    "answer": "i will have"
  },
  {
    "id": 2244,
    "question": "daría",
    "questionDetails": "Daría todo lo que tengo para vivir en París.",
    "answer": "i would give",
    "answerDetails": "I would give everything I have to live in Paris."
  },
  {
    "id": 2245,
    "question": "calla",
    "questionDetails": "Vamos, ve a tu cuarto y calla.",
    "answer": "shut up, hush, shut",
    "answerDetails": "Go on, get in that room and shut up."
  },
  {
    "id": 2246,
    "question": "entramos",
    "questionDetails": "Entramos en la edad de oro",
    "answer": "walked, stepped",
    "answerDetails": "Walked into the golden age."
  },
  {
    "id": 2247,
    "question": "dejarme",
    "questionDetails": "Nos separamos hace 2 meses, y Marisa todavía se niega a dejarme. Me llama cada semana.",
    "answer": "let me go",
    "answerDetails": "We broke up two months ago, and Marisa still refuses to let me go. She calls me every week."
  },
  {
    "id": 2248,
    "question": "entienden",
    "questionDetails": "Me pregunto si lo entienden.",
    "answer": "understand",
    "answerDetails": "I wonder if you understand this."
  },
  {
    "id": 2249,
    "question": "precioso",
    "questionDetails": "Un lote precioso que usted sabe sobre los perros!.",
    "answer": "precious",
    "answerDetails": "A precious lot you know about dogs!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2250,
    "question": "abrió",
    "answer": "Opened"
  },
  {
    "id": 2251,
    "question": "ambos",
    "questionDetails": "Tenía a una persona a ambos lados de mí en el avión.",
    "answer": "either",
    "answerDetails": "There was a person on either side of me on the plane."
  },
  {
    "id": 2252,
    "question": "fatal",
    "questionDetails": "La herida no era inmediatamente fatal.",
    "answer": "fatal, terrible, fatale",
    "answerDetails": "The wound was not immediately fatal."
  },
  {
    "id": 2253,
    "question": "posibilidades",
    "questionDetails": "Su idea de negocios tiene excelentes posibilidades.",
    "answer": "possibilities",
    "answerDetails": "Her business idea has great possibilities."
  },
  {
    "id": 2254,
    "question": "miro",
    "questionDetails": "Miro a las estrellas.",
    "answer": "look",
    "answerDetails": "Look up at the stars."
  },
  {
    "id": 2255,
    "question": "doce",
    "questionDetails": "Hace doce horas estábamos destruidos.",
    "answer": "twelve",
    "answerDetails": "Twelve hours ago we were all wrecked."
  },
  {
    "id": 2256,
    "question": "nacido",
    "questionDetails": "Los niños nacidos en esto países tienen una esperanza de vida más corta.",
    "answer": "born",
    "answerDetails": "Children born in these countries have a shorter life expectancy."
  },
  {
    "id": 2257,
    "question": "maldita",
    "questionDetails": "Lo primero en la maldita mañana.",
    "answer": "bloody, frakking, curse",
    "answerDetails": "First thing in the bloody morning."
  },
  {
    "id": 2258,
    "question": "propuesta",
    "questionDetails": "Su propuesta para el nuevo programa de TV suena interesante.",
    "answer": "proposal, proposition",
    "answerDetails": "Your proposal for the new TV program sounds interesting."
  },
  {
    "id": 2259,
    "question": "enamorada",
    "questionDetails": "Descubrí que estaba enamorada de mí.",
    "answer": "crush, love",
    "answerDetails": "I discovered he had a crush on me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2260,
    "question": "rosa",
    "questionDetails": "Creo que te quedaría bien ese pantalón rosa.",
    "answer": "pink, rose",
    "answerDetails": "I think those pink pants would look great on you."
  },
  {
    "id": 2261,
    "question": "europa",
    "answer": "Europe"
  },
  {
    "id": 2262,
    "question": "despacho",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo una reunión en mi despacho y no quiero que me interrumpan.",
    "answer": "office, dispatch, chambers",
    "answerDetails": "I have a meeting in my office and don’t want to be interrupted."
  },
  {
    "id": 2263,
    "question": "legal",
    "questionDetails": "Después de salir de la cárcel, Logan decidió empezar un negocio legal.",
    "answer": "legitimate",
    "answerDetails": "After getting out of jail, Logan decided to start a legitimate business."
  },
  {
    "id": 2264,
    "question": "tarea",
    "questionDetails": "El crecimiento de la tarea y del trabajo a tiempo parcial.",
    "answer": "homework, assignment",
    "answerDetails": "The growth of homework and of part-time working."
  },
  {
    "id": 2265,
    "question": "herida",
    "questionDetails": "Mi herida no ha sanado aún.",
    "answer": "wound",
    "answerDetails": "My wound hasn’t healed yet."
  },
  {
    "id": 2266,
    "question": "crimen",
    "questionDetails": "Todavía no se encuentra al autor del crimen de aquella turista.",
    "answer": "murder",
    "answerDetails": "They still haven’t found the person responsible for the murder of that tourist."
  },
  {
    "id": 2267,
    "question": "tienda",
    "questionDetails": "Fuimos a la tienda a comprar unas toallas.",
    "answer": "store, shop",
    "answerDetails": "We went to the store to buy some towels."
  },
  {
    "id": 2268,
    "question": "cadáver",
    "questionDetails": "Creía que el fascismo reviviría el cadáver de Europa.",
    "answer": "corpse, carcass",
    "answerDetails": "He believed that fascism would revive the corpse of Europe."
  },
  {
    "id": 2269,
    "question": "necesites",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo todo lo que necesites aquí atrás.",
    "answer": "need",
    "answerDetails": "I got everything you need back there."
  },
  {
    "id": 2270,
    "question": "emergencia",
    "questionDetails": "Yo cuento desde emergencia de una anomalía integral …",
    "answer": "emergence",
    "answerDetails": "I count from the emergence of one integral anomaly …"
  },
  {
    "id": 2271,
    "question": "disculpen",
    "questionDetails": "Muy bien, disculpen.",
    "answer": "excuse me, sorry, pardon me",
    "answerDetails": "All right, excuse me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2272,
    "question": "crear",
    "questionDetails": "Al girar la manija, podemos crear un mundo.",
    "answer": "make",
    "answerDetails": "By making a handle, you can make a world."
  },
  {
    "id": 2273,
    "question": "dejando",
    "questionDetails": "Alguien está dejando un rastro.",
    "answer": "leaving, letting, allowing",
    "answerDetails": "Someone is leaving a trail."
  },
  {
    "id": 2274,
    "question": "pagan",
    "questionDetails": "La mayoría de los hombres no me pagan para hablar.",
    "answer": "pay",
    "answerDetails": "Most men don’t pay me to talk."
  },
  {
    "id": 2275,
    "question": "esperas",
    "questionDetails": "Por la persona que menos esperas.",
    "answer": "expect, waitings, delays",
    "answerDetails": "By the person you’d least expect."
  },
  {
    "id": 2276,
    "question": "saqué",
    "answer": "Took"
  },
  {
    "id": 2277,
    "question": "nací",
    "questionDetails": "No hubo alegría cuando yo nací.",
    "answer": "was born, born",
    "answerDetails": "There was no gladness when i was born."
  },
  {
    "id": 2278,
    "question": "tocado",
    "questionDetails": "La estrella dijo que estaba ‘ muy tocado ‘ para recibir su medalla.",
    "answer": "touched, hairdo, headpiece",
    "answerDetails": "The star said he was ‘very touched’ to receive his medal."
  },
  {
    "id": 2279,
    "question": "despertar",
    "questionDetails": "El despertar del vigoroso debate político.",
    "answer": "awakening",
    "answerDetails": "The awakening of vigorous political debate."
  },
  {
    "id": 2280,
    "question": "preguntó",
    "questionDetails": "Le preguntó a su maestro cómo se encuentra la raíz cuadrada de 17.",
    "answer": "she asked",
    "answerDetails": "She asked her teacher how to find the square root of 17."
  },
  {
    "id": 2281,
    "question": "recibido",
    "questionDetails": "Habrán recibido mi carta.",
    "answer": "received, greeted, welcomed",
    "answerDetails": "They must’ve received my letter."
  },
  {
    "id": 2282,
    "question": "cuentes",
    "questionDetails": "Salvo que cuentes aquellos en contra de la naturaleza.",
    "answer": "count",
    "answerDetails": "Unless you count the ones against nature."
  },
  {
    "id": 2283,
    "question": "tuyos",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo que los tuyos aparecieron en las primeras horas.",
    "answer": "yours",
    "answerDetails": "Just yours started the first two hours."
  },
  {
    "id": 2284,
    "question": "aun",
    "questionDetails": "Aun si pudiera, no lo necesitó.",
    "answer": "even, still, yet",
    "answerDetails": "Even if he could, he didn’t need to."
  },
  {
    "id": 2285,
    "question": "pedimos",
    "questionDetails": "Pedimos más agua porque teníamos sed.",
    "answer": "we asked",
    "answerDetails": "We asked for more water because we were thirsty."
  },
  {
    "id": 2286,
    "question": "date",
    "questionDetails": "Date la vuelta y pon las manos en el mostrador.",
    "answer": "turn",
    "answerDetails": "Turn around, put your hands on the counter."
  },
  {
    "id": 2287,
    "question": "gritos",
    "questionDetails": "Unos Gritos fuertes en la guardería hicieron que los padres entraran corriendo aterrorizados.",
    "answer": "screaming, shouting, yelling",
    "answerDetails": "A loud screaming in the nursery caused the parents to run in a panic."
  },
  {
    "id": 2288,
    "question": "nariz",
    "questionDetails": "Caminó más allá de los coches con la nariz en el aire.",
    "answer": "nose",
    "answerDetails": "She walked past the cars with her nose in the air."
  },
  {
    "id": 2289,
    "question": "mandan",
    "questionDetails": "Dame la dirección adonde mandan las entradas.",
    "answer": "send",
    "answerDetails": "Punch up the address where you send the tickets."
  },
  {
    "id": 2290,
    "question": "encuentras",
    "questionDetails": "Y exactamente al mismo tiempo encuentras a otra persona.",
    "answer": "find",
    "answerDetails": "And exactly the same time find someone else."
  },
  {
    "id": 2291,
    "question": "comido",
    "questionDetails": "Pudo haber comido mariscos o maní.",
    "answer": "eaten",
    "answerDetails": "Could have eaten shellfish or peanuts."
  },
  {
    "id": 2292,
    "question": "rompió",
    "questionDetails": "Me rompió el reloj y no lo quiere pagar.",
    "answer": "she broke, it broke",
    "answerDetails": "She broke my watch and she won’t pay for it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2293,
    "question": "primeras",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo que los tuyos aparecieron en las primeras horas.",
    "answer": "first, early",
    "answerDetails": "Just yours started the first two hours."
  },
  {
    "id": 2294,
    "question": "pequeños",
    "questionDetails": "Me siento cómodo hablando en grupos pequeños.",
    "answer": "small, little, tiny",
    "answerDetails": "I am perfectly comfortable speaking to small groups."
  },
  {
    "id": 2295,
    "question": "ponía",
    "questionDetails": "Ponía comida sobre la mesa.",
    "answer": "put, wore",
    "answerDetails": "I put food on the table."
  },
  {
    "id": 2296,
    "question": "andas",
    "answer": "bier"
  },
  {
    "id": 2297,
    "question": "amante",
    "questionDetails": "Esta donación fue hecha por una amante de las artes.",
    "answer": "lover",
    "answerDetails": "This donation was made by a lover of the arts."
  },
  {
    "id": 2298,
    "question": "bella",
    "questionDetails": "Esa cosa es la más bella.",
    "answer": "beautiful, Belle, beauty",
    "answerDetails": "That thing is the most beautiful."
  },
  {
    "id": 2299,
    "question": "enemigo",
    "questionDetails": "Desde ahí podréis neutralizar cualquier intento de subida del enemigo.",
    "answer": "enemy",
    "answerDetails": "From here you can suppress any enemy attempt at climbing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2300,
    "question": "lograr",
    "questionDetails": "Pensamos que lograríamos más este año.",
    "answer": "accomplish, reach",
    "answerDetails": "We thought we would accomplish more this year."
  },
  {
    "id": 2301,
    "question": "paciente",
    "questionDetails": "Un paciente puede estar ausente.",
    "answer": "patient",
    "answerDetails": "A patient might be missing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2302,
    "question": "gorda",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre hablaba de lo gorda que estaba.",
    "answer": "fat, fatso, plump",
    "answerDetails": "She would talk about how fat she was."
  },
  {
    "id": 2303,
    "question": "tranquilízate",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Tranquilízate ya mismo!-¡ No me voy a tranquilizar!.",
    "answer": "calm yourself",
    "answerDetails": "Calm yourself right now!-I will not calm myself!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2304,
    "question": "baje",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dónde está la biblioteca?-Baje al primer piso.",
    "answer": "go downstairs",
    "answerDetails": "Where’s the library?-Go downstairs to the first floor."
  },
  {
    "id": 2305,
    "question": "repito",
    "questionDetails": "No, repito, no cambio pañales.",
    "answer": "repeat",
    "answerDetails": "I do not, repeat, do not change diapers."
  },
  {
    "id": 2306,
    "question": "genio",
    "questionDetails": "Juanita está aprendiendo a controlar su genio.",
    "answer": "temper",
    "answerDetails": "Juanita is learning to control her temper."
  },
  {
    "id": 2307,
    "question": "desapareció",
    "answer": "he was gone"
  },
  {
    "id": 2308,
    "question": "civil",
    "questionDetails": "Es un tribunal civil.",
    "answer": "civil, marital, calendar",
    "answerDetails": "This is a civil court."
  },
  {
    "id": 2309,
    "question": "explicaciones",
    "questionDetails": "Otras tablas podrían también usar explicaciones más completas.",
    "answer": "explanations",
    "answerDetails": "Other charts could also use more comprehensible explanations."
  },
  {
    "id": 2310,
    "question": "acompañe",
    "questionDetails": "Invito a la prensa a que me acompañe.",
    "answer": "accompany, escort",
    "answerDetails": "I invite the media to accompany me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2311,
    "question": "consiguió",
    "questionDetails": "Me encanta su chaqueta. Creo que la consiguió en Europa.",
    "answer": "got it, it got",
    "answerDetails": "I love his jacket. I think he got it in Europe."
  },
  {
    "id": 2312,
    "question": "echó",
    "questionDetails": "Pero su amiga echó atrás la cabeza.",
    "answer": "threw, burst, cast",
    "answerDetails": "But her friend threw back his head."
  },
  {
    "id": 2313,
    "question": "despedida",
    "questionDetails": "Linda hizo su despedida a su familia.",
    "answer": "farewell, parting",
    "answerDetails": "Linda bid farewell to her family."
  },
  {
    "id": 2314,
    "question": "esperen",
    "questionDetails": "Denle esto personalmente, y esperen.",
    "answer": "wait, expect, await",
    "answerDetails": "Give this to him personally, then wait."
  },
  {
    "id": 2315,
    "question": "viera",
    "questionDetails": "Debí asegurarme de que no la viera.",
    "answer": "see",
    "answerDetails": "I should have made sure she didn’t see it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2316,
    "question": "preparada",
    "questionDetails": "Yo nunca esperé que vinieras preparada.",
    "answer": "prepared, ready, poised",
    "answerDetails": "I never expected that, that you’d come prepared."
  },
  {
    "id": 2317,
    "question": "difíciles",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo que hacer algunas preguntas difíciles.",
    "answer": "difficult, hard, tough",
    "answerDetails": "I must make some difficult questions."
  },
  {
    "id": 2318,
    "question": "lujo",
    "questionDetails": "Un buen baño en el jacuzzi con una barra de chocolate oscuro. ¡ Qué lujo!.",
    "answer": "luxury",
    "answerDetails": "A soak in the hot tub with a bar of dark chocolate. What luxury!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2319,
    "question": "pata",
    "questionDetails": "¿Prefieres la carne blanca o la pata?",
    "answer": "leg, paw",
    "answerDetails": "Do you prefer the white meat or the leg?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2320,
    "question": "verlos",
    "answer": "See"
  },
  {
    "id": 2321,
    "question": "remedio",
    "questionDetails": "Ya no tiene remedio.",
    "answer": "remedy, choice, cure",
    "answerDetails": "It’s past remedy."
  },
  {
    "id": 2322,
    "question": "escondido",
    "answer": "secluded"
  },
  {
    "id": 2323,
    "question": "pasara",
    "questionDetails": "Y en este enojo, no se que te pasara.",
    "answer": "happen",
    "answerDetails": "And this madness, don’t know what happen to you."
  },
  {
    "id": 2324,
    "question": "trabajas",
    "questionDetails": "¿Trabajas en el departamento de la informática?",
    "answer": "do you work",
    "answerDetails": "Do you work in IT?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2325,
    "question": "tendríamos",
    "questionDetails": "Se suponía que tendríamos una cena tranquila.",
    "answer": "have",
    "answerDetails": "We were supposed to have a quiet dinner."
  },
  {
    "id": 2326,
    "question": "haremos",
    "questionDetails": "Haremos un comedero de madera para los pájaros.",
    "answer": "we will make",
    "answerDetails": "We will make a bird feeder out of wood."
  },
  {
    "id": 2327,
    "question": "sentar",
    "questionDetails": "Nosotras nos vamos a sentar acá.",
    "answer": "sit, lay, sit down",
    "answerDetails": "We were going to sit there."
  },
  {
    "id": 2328,
    "question": "aplauso",
    "questionDetails": "Me encanta escuchar el aplauso del público tras la actuación.",
    "answer": "clap",
    "answerDetails": "I love to hear the clap of the audience at the end of a performance."
  },
  {
    "id": 2329,
    "question": "diré",
    "questionDetails": "Juro que diré la verdad.",
    "answer": "i will tell",
    "answerDetails": "I swear I will tell the truth."
  },
  {
    "id": 2330,
    "question": "perdida",
    "questionDetails": "Me ha devuelto mi perdida juventud.",
    "answer": "lost, loss, missing",
    "answerDetails": "She has returned to me again my lost youth."
  },
  {
    "id": 2331,
    "question": "podrás",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que podrás hacerlo.",
    "answer": "can",
    "answerDetails": "I know you can."
  },
  {
    "id": 2332,
    "question": "ritmo",
    "questionDetails": "Por favor, ve más despacio. No puedo caminar a tu mismo ritmo.",
    "answer": "pace, rhythm, beat",
    "answerDetails": "Please, slow down. I can’t walk at your same pace."
  },
  {
    "id": 2333,
    "question": "aires",
    "answer": "Aires"
  },
  {
    "id": 2334,
    "question": "viernes",
    "answer": "Friday"
  },
  {
    "id": 2335,
    "question": "miguel",
    "answer": "Miguel"
  },
  {
    "id": 2336,
    "question": "sos",
    "answer": "SOS"
  },
  {
    "id": 2337,
    "question": "jefa",
    "questionDetails": "La jefa les dijo que enviaran las mercancías.",
    "answer": "boss",
    "answerDetails": "The boss told them to deliver the goods."
  },
  {
    "id": 2338,
    "question": "ama",
    "questionDetails": "Yo la amo, y ella me ama a mí.",
    "answer": "she loves",
    "answerDetails": "I love her, and she loves me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2339,
    "question": "prima",
    "questionDetails": "Si logras tu meta de ventas durante 8 semanas consecutivas, la compañía te regala una prima de $500.",
    "answer": "bonus",
    "answerDetails": "If you hit your sales goal for 8 consecutive weeks, the company gives you a $500 bonus."
  },
  {
    "id": 2340,
    "question": "andan",
    "questionDetails": "Dicen que aquí las cosas no andan bien.",
    "answer": "are",
    "answerDetails": "They say things are no good in this house."
  },
  {
    "id": 2341,
    "question": "capital",
    "questionDetails": "Mi padre me dejó la mitad del capital.",
    "answer": "capital, equity, principal",
    "answerDetails": "My father left me half the capital."
  },
  {
    "id": 2342,
    "question": "acuérdate",
    "questionDetails": "Acuérdate de por qué lo estamos haciendo.",
    "answer": "remember",
    "answerDetails": "Remember why we´re doing this."
  },
  {
    "id": 2343,
    "question": "negar",
    "questionDetails": "Obviamente,quería negar que estaba en un casino.",
    "answer": "deny",
    "answerDetails": "Obviously he was tryingto deny it was a gambling house."
  },
  {
    "id": 2344,
    "question": "cuidando",
    "questionDetails": "Me querías en casa cuidando de los niños.",
    "answer": "taking care, caring, minding",
    "answerDetails": "You wanted me at home taking care of the kids."
  },
  {
    "id": 2345,
    "question": "enterado",
    "questionDetails": "Algunos críticos enterados la consideran la mejor novela del siglo.",
    "answer": "knowledgeable",
    "answerDetails": "Some knowledgeable critics consider it the best novel of the century."
  },
  {
    "id": 2346,
    "question": "pásame",
    "questionDetails": "Pásame el bote de las galletas.",
    "answer": "pass, Gimme",
    "answerDetails": "Pass the biscuit barrel."
  },
  {
    "id": 2347,
    "question": "patas",
    "questionDetails": "Debe tener prisa, mueve las patas rápidamente.",
    "answer": "pins",
    "answerDetails": "He must be in a hurry. His pins are moving fast."
  },
  {
    "id": 2348,
    "question": "volviste",
    "questionDetails": "Porque tú te volviste un problema.",
    "answer": "become",
    "answerDetails": "Because you become a problem."
  },
  {
    "id": 2349,
    "question": "sigamos",
    "questionDetails": "Prefiero que sigamos con el protocolo.",
    "answer": "follow",
    "answerDetails": "I prefer to follow the protocol."
  },
  {
    "id": 2350,
    "question": "pongan",
    "questionDetails": "Pongan sus cajas a un lado.",
    "answer": "put",
    "answerDetails": "Put your lockers away."
  },
  {
    "id": 2351,
    "question": "soltar",
    "questionDetails": "Activistas soltaron los chimpancés de sus jaulas.",
    "answer": "free, drop",
    "answerDetails": "Activists freed the chimps from their cages."
  },
  {
    "id": 2352,
    "question": "comunicación",
    "questionDetails": "Demoler las convenciones de su comunicación.",
    "answer": "communication",
    "answerDetails": "To undermine the conventions of its communication."
  },
  {
    "id": 2353,
    "question": "paro",
    "questionDetails": "El paro ha empujado a muchos jóvenes a marcharse del país.",
    "answer": "unemployment, stoppage, strike",
    "answerDetails": "Unemployment has driven many young people to leave the country."
  },
  {
    "id": 2354,
    "question": "invitado",
    "questionDetails": "El Dr. Gervais será un conferenciante invitado en el congreso.",
    "answer": "visiting",
    "answerDetails": "Dr. Gervais will be a visiting speaker at the conference."
  },
  {
    "id": 2355,
    "question": "bola",
    "questionDetails": "La forma en que se colocan las bolas depende del juego de billar que estés jugando.",
    "answer": "ball, fib",
    "answerDetails": "The way you rack the balls depends on which game of billiards you’re playing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2356,
    "question": "números",
    "questionDetails": "Comprobamos los números de serie y coincidieron.",
    "answer": "numbers, numerals, issues",
    "answerDetails": "We checked the serial numbers and they matched."
  },
  {
    "id": 2357,
    "question": "desaparecido",
    "questionDetails": "Militares enumerados como desaparecidos en acción.",
    "answer": "missing",
    "answerDetails": "Servicemen listed as missing in action."
  },
  {
    "id": 2358,
    "question": "pollo",
    "questionDetails": "El pollo está delicioso.",
    "answer": "chicken",
    "answerDetails": "The chicken is delicious."
  },
  {
    "id": 2359,
    "question": "ocurrir",
    "questionDetails": "No puedo creer lo que acaba de ocurrir.",
    "answer": "happen",
    "answerDetails": "I can’t believe what just happened."
  },
  {
    "id": 2360,
    "question": "estrellas",
    "questionDetails": "Algunas personas vienen aquí para ser estrellas.",
    "answer": "star",
    "answerDetails": "Some people come here to be a star."
  },
  {
    "id": 2361,
    "question": "acordar",
    "questionDetails": "Acordaron que había que limpiar el parque.",
    "answer": "agree",
    "answerDetails": "They agreed that the park needed to be cleaned up."
  },
  {
    "id": 2362,
    "question": "probable",
    "questionDetails": "Especulación sobre el efecto probable de optar por.",
    "answer": "likely",
    "answerDetails": "Speculation on the likely effect of opting out."
  },
  {
    "id": 2363,
    "question": "viniendo",
    "questionDetails": "Los buques estan viniendo por nosotros.",
    "answer": "coming, comin’",
    "answerDetails": "The boats are coming for us."
  },
  {
    "id": 2364,
    "question": "construir",
    "questionDetails": "A partir de estos datos, podemos construir modelos que pronostiquen el comportamiento de las variables.",
    "answer": "construct",
    "answerDetails": "From this data, we can construct predictive models for the variables."
  },
  {
    "id": 2365,
    "question": "comienza",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando Amos Le dice a Joan que la deja, ella comienza a llorar.",
    "answer": "she begins, he starts, it begins",
    "answerDetails": "When Amos tells Joan he’s leaving her, she begins to cry."
  },
  {
    "id": 2366,
    "question": "agente",
    "questionDetails": "Descubrieron que era Agente Secreto del FBI.",
    "answer": "agent, broker",
    "answerDetails": "He was unmasked as an undercover agent for the FBI."
  },
  {
    "id": 2367,
    "question": "boda",
    "answer": "Wedding"
  },
  {
    "id": 2368,
    "question": "ja",
    "questionDetails": "Me dijo que el auto era suyo. ¡ Ja!, sé de buena tinta que es de su hermano.",
    "answer": "ha",
    "answerDetails": "He told me the car was his. Ha! I know very well that it’s his brother’s."
  },
  {
    "id": 2369,
    "question": "oigan",
    "answer": "Hey, yo"
  },
  {
    "id": 2370,
    "question": "créeme",
    "questionDetails": "No quieres estar cerca de Charlottle cuando está enojada. Créeme.",
    "answer": "trust me",
    "answerDetails": "You don’t want to be around Charlotte when she’s angry. Trust me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2371,
    "question": "madrid",
    "answer": "Madrid"
  },
  {
    "id": 2372,
    "question": "visitar",
    "questionDetails": "Si quieren visitar el castillo, hay que reservar con antelación.",
    "answer": "go around",
    "answerDetails": "If you want to go around the castle, you have to book in advance."
  },
  {
    "id": 2373,
    "question": "acepto",
    "questionDetails": "Te acepto como eres, cariño.",
    "answer": "accept, agree",
    "answerDetails": "I accept you the way you are, darling."
  },
  {
    "id": 2374,
    "question": "matan",
    "questionDetails": "Los favores matan antes que una bala.",
    "answer": "kill",
    "answerDetails": "Favor going to kill you faster than a bullet."
  },
  {
    "id": 2375,
    "question": "investigar",
    "questionDetails": "Estudios futuros investigarán si el uso a largo plazo de los fármacos podría prevenir el cáncer.",
    "answer": "investigate",
    "answerDetails": "Future studies will investigate whether long-term use of the drugs could prevent cancer."
  },
  {
    "id": 2376,
    "question": "verá",
    "answer": "See"
  },
  {
    "id": 2377,
    "question": "protección",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando estoy en el taller, siempre utilizo guantes como protección para evitar accidentes.",
    "answer": "guard, protection",
    "answerDetails": "At the repair shop, I always wear gloves as a guard against accidents."
  },
  {
    "id": 2378,
    "question": "besos",
    "questionDetails": "Tres besos dicen que es un vínculo amoroso.",
    "answer": "kisses",
    "answerDetails": "Three kisses says it’s a romantic attachment."
  },
  {
    "id": 2379,
    "question": "respetar",
    "questionDetails": "Respetaremos sus deseos y esparciremos sus cenizas en el desierto.",
    "answer": "respect, observe",
    "answerDetails": "We will respect his wishes and will scatter his ashes in the desert."
  },
  {
    "id": 2380,
    "question": "pagando",
    "questionDetails": "Ya estoy pagando por ello.",
    "answer": "paying, payin",
    "answerDetails": "I already am paying for it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2381,
    "question": "chino",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy estudiando chino en la universidad.",
    "answer": "chinese",
    "answerDetails": "I’m studying Chinese at university."
  },
  {
    "id": 2382,
    "question": "sentimientos",
    "questionDetails": "Me heriste mucho los sentimientos.",
    "answer": "feelings",
    "answerDetails": "You really hurt my feelings."
  },
  {
    "id": 2383,
    "question": "mereces",
    "questionDetails": "Tú mereces más que eso.",
    "answer": "deserve",
    "answerDetails": "You deserve more than this."
  },
  {
    "id": 2384,
    "question": "sepan",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que sepan lo genial que puedes ser.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "I want them to know how great you can be."
  },
  {
    "id": 2385,
    "question": "sueldo",
    "questionDetails": "Su sueldo es bastante bueno, pero gasta demasiado en su carro.",
    "answer": "salary, wage",
    "answerDetails": "She earns a fair salary, but she spends too much on her car."
  },
  {
    "id": 2386,
    "question": "ciento",
    "questionDetails": "Ciento trece kilos con cincuenta gramos.",
    "answer": "hundred",
    "answerDetails": "A hundred and thirteen kilos and fifty grams."
  },
  {
    "id": 2387,
    "question": "escuche",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces escuche la música, no la canción.",
    "answer": "listen, hear",
    "answerDetails": "Then listen to the music, not the song."
  },
  {
    "id": 2388,
    "question": "oferta",
    "questionDetails": "Han hecho una oferta de 575 millones de dólares por la empresa.",
    "answer": "bid, tender, sale",
    "answerDetails": "They’ve made a bid of 575 million dollars for the company."
  },
  {
    "id": 2389,
    "question": "verdadera",
    "questionDetails": "Y en los próximos días te probaré mi verdadera dedicación.",
    "answer": "true, real, genuine",
    "answerDetails": "And the next few days will prove my true devotion."
  },
  {
    "id": 2390,
    "question": "preguntarle",
    "questionDetails": "No quiero preguntarle. Quiero averiguar la respuesta por mí mismo.",
    "answer": "ask him",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t want to ask him. I want to figure out the answer by myself."
  },
  {
    "id": 2391,
    "question": "descansa",
    "questionDetails": "La mente humana jamás descansa.",
    "answer": "rest, relies",
    "answerDetails": "The human mind is never at rest."
  },
  {
    "id": 2392,
    "question": "encantan",
    "questionDetails": "A las cabras les encantan las tartas.",
    "answer": "love, enchant, adore",
    "answerDetails": "Goats really love pie."
  },
  {
    "id": 2393,
    "question": "esconder",
    "questionDetails": "Tampoco tenemos nada que esconder.",
    "answer": "conceal",
    "answerDetails": "Neither have we anything to conceal."
  },
  {
    "id": 2394,
    "question": "salgas",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca salgas de la ciudad.",
    "answer": "leave",
    "answerDetails": "Never leave the city."
  },
  {
    "id": 2395,
    "question": "estudios",
    "questionDetails": "Milena piensa seguir sus estudios en Europa.",
    "answer": "studies, education",
    "answerDetails": "Milena’s planning to continue her studies in Europe."
  },
  {
    "id": 2396,
    "question": "decide",
    "answer": "Decides"
  },
  {
    "id": 2397,
    "question": "escena",
    "questionDetails": "No Montes una escena delante de los niños.",
    "answer": "scene",
    "answerDetails": "Don’t make a scene in front of the children."
  },
  {
    "id": 2398,
    "question": "echo",
    "answer": "he threw"
  },
  {
    "id": 2399,
    "question": "curso",
    "questionDetails": "Mi decisión había parecido a ser el curso más sabio abierto a mí en el momento.",
    "answer": "course, progress, academic year",
    "answerDetails": "My decision had seemed to be the wisest course open to me at the time."
  },
  {
    "id": 2400,
    "question": "hacías",
    "questionDetails": "Haz lo que hacías antes.",
    "answer": "did",
    "answerDetails": "Go back to what you did before."
  },
  {
    "id": 2401,
    "question": "central",
    "questionDetails": "La central no genera suficiente electricidad para abastecer a toda la ciudad.",
    "answer": "power station, core, headquarters",
    "answerDetails": "The power station doesn’t generate enough electricity to power the whole city."
  },
  {
    "id": 2402,
    "question": "ocurrido",
    "questionDetails": "Y que el fallo había ocurrido por esas alteraciones.",
    "answer": "occurred, happened, transpired",
    "answerDetails": "And that the failure occurred because of those alterations."
  },
  {
    "id": 2403,
    "question": "responde",
    "questionDetails": "Veamos si el universo responde.",
    "answer": "responds, answer, replies",
    "answerDetails": "Let us see if the universe responds."
  },
  {
    "id": 2404,
    "question": "descanso",
    "questionDetails": "Un breve descanso entre ejercicios es esencial para un entrenamiento óptimo.",
    "answer": "rest, break, relaxation",
    "answerDetails": "A short rest between exercises is essential for an optimum workout."
  },
  {
    "id": 2405,
    "question": "míralo",
    "answer": "Look"
  },
  {
    "id": 2406,
    "question": "convertido",
    "questionDetails": "Dicen que ha convertido a cientos más.",
    "answer": "converted",
    "answerDetails": "They say he converted hundreds more."
  },
  {
    "id": 2407,
    "question": "estaríamos",
    "questionDetails": "Todos estaríamos como clase mucho mejor situados.",
    "answer": "would",
    "answerDetails": "The whole class would do better."
  },
  {
    "id": 2408,
    "question": "inútil",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre he sido inútil en la cocina.",
    "answer": "useless, futile, worthless",
    "answerDetails": "I’ve always been useless in the kitchen."
  },
  {
    "id": 2409,
    "question": "decidimos",
    "questionDetails": "Decidimos que nuestro único rival es el teatro.",
    "answer": "decided",
    "answerDetails": "We have decided our only rival is the theatre."
  },
  {
    "id": 2410,
    "question": "empiezan",
    "questionDetails": "Las piezas empiezan a encajar.",
    "answer": "begin, start",
    "answerDetails": "The final pieces begin to fall into shape."
  },
  {
    "id": 2411,
    "question": "subiendo",
    "questionDetails": "Y está subiendo el índice de audiencia.",
    "answer": "climbing, rising, up",
    "answerDetails": "And our ratings are climbing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2412,
    "question": "pablo",
    "answer": "Pablo"
  },
  {
    "id": 2413,
    "question": "princesa",
    "questionDetails": "La princesa de la política americana.",
    "answer": "princess",
    "answerDetails": "The princess of American politics."
  },
  {
    "id": 2414,
    "question": "barco",
    "questionDetails": "Como tenemos una casa en la costa, estamos pensando en comprarnos un barco.",
    "answer": "boat, ship, vessel",
    "answerDetails": "Since we live on the coast, we’re thinking about buying a boat."
  },
  {
    "id": 2415,
    "question": "ayudes",
    "answer": "help"
  },
  {
    "id": 2416,
    "question": "investigando",
    "questionDetails": "Estamos investigando la causa ahora.",
    "answer": "investigating, researching, inquiring",
    "answerDetails": "We are investigating the cause."
  },
  {
    "id": 2417,
    "question": "estúpido",
    "questionDetails": "¡ No eres un cobarde, estúpido!.",
    "answer": "stupid",
    "answerDetails": "You’re not a coward, stupid!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2418,
    "question": "salgan",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos ordenado a todos que salgan de la ciudad.",
    "answer": "out",
    "answerDetails": "We have ordered everyone out of the city."
  },
  {
    "id": 2419,
    "question": "buscarla",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces, ve a buscarla.",
    "answer": "her",
    "answerDetails": "Then go get her."
  },
  {
    "id": 2420,
    "question": "montar",
    "questionDetails": "Montaron cañones a ambos lados del barco de guerra.",
    "answer": "mount, ride",
    "answerDetails": "They mounted guns on both sides of the battleship."
  },
  {
    "id": 2421,
    "question": "arrepentir",
    "questionDetails": "Si te juntas con él, te vas a arrepentir.",
    "answer": "regret",
    "answerDetails": "You hook up with him and you’ll regret it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2422,
    "question": "sigas",
    "questionDetails": "Prende de ellos, pero no los sigas.",
    "answer": "follow",
    "answerDetails": "Learn from them, but do not follow."
  },
  {
    "id": 2423,
    "question": "haberme",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca debí haberme ido.",
    "answer": "have",
    "answerDetails": "I should have never gone away."
  },
  {
    "id": 2424,
    "question": "aguanto",
    "questionDetails": "Ya no aguanto esta ropa.",
    "answer": "stand",
    "answerDetails": "I can’t stand these clothes anymore."
  },
  {
    "id": 2425,
    "question": "mentiroso",
    "answer": "lying"
  },
  {
    "id": 2426,
    "question": "organizar",
    "questionDetails": "Subí al ático para organizarlo y me ensucié.",
    "answer": "organize, arrange",
    "answerDetails": "I went up to organize the attic and I got dirty."
  },
  {
    "id": 2427,
    "question": "personaje",
    "questionDetails": "Mi abuela era todo un personaje.",
    "answer": "character",
    "answerDetails": "My grandmother was a real character."
  },
  {
    "id": 2428,
    "question": "encantada",
    "questionDetails": "Encantada de conocerle, señor.",
    "answer": "delighted, enchanted, haunted",
    "answerDetails": "Delighted to have met you, sire."
  },
  {
    "id": 2429,
    "question": "alcanza",
    "questionDetails": "Es que alcanza a pensar en el más mínimo detalle.",
    "answer": "reaches, achieves, attains",
    "answerDetails": "It reaches to think in the smallest detail."
  },
  {
    "id": 2430,
    "question": "pensaste",
    "questionDetails": "Tú pensaste que no había ido a verte bailar.",
    "answer": "thought, youthought",
    "answerDetails": "You thought she didn’t come to see you dance."
  },
  {
    "id": 2431,
    "question": "caballeros",
    "questionDetails": "Gracias por el whisky, caballeros.",
    "answer": "gentlemen, knights, gents",
    "answerDetails": "Thanks for the drink, gentlemen."
  },
  {
    "id": 2432,
    "question": "muriendo",
    "questionDetails": "El sol de este sistema está muriendo.",
    "answer": "dying, dyin’",
    "answerDetails": "The sun in this system is dying."
  },
  {
    "id": 2433,
    "question": "dirá",
    "questionDetails": "Tu amigo te dirá los detalles.",
    "answer": "tell",
    "answerDetails": "Your friend will tell you the details."
  },
  {
    "id": 2434,
    "question": "tratamiento",
    "questionDetails": "El tratamiento del tejido elimina las cualidades no deseadas.",
    "answer": "processing",
    "answerDetails": "The processing of the fabric eliminates undesirable qualities."
  },
  {
    "id": 2435,
    "question": "diera",
    "questionDetails": "Me pidió que le diera esta carta.",
    "answer": "give",
    "answerDetails": "He asked me to give you this letter."
  },
  {
    "id": 2436,
    "question": "magia",
    "questionDetails": "De repente, como por la magia, las puertas comienzan a abrirse.",
    "answer": "magic",
    "answerDetails": "Suddenly, as if by magic, the doors start to open."
  },
  {
    "id": 2437,
    "question": "tenerlo",
    "questionDetails": "Ese coche deportivo es increíble. Haría cualquier cosa por tenerlo.",
    "answer": "have it",
    "answerDetails": "That sports car is amazing. I’d do anything to have it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2438,
    "question": "paquete",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes comprar el software como paquete y ahorrar dinero en cada artículo.",
    "answer": "bundle",
    "answerDetails": "You can buy the software as a bundle and save money on each individual item."
  },
  {
    "id": 2439,
    "question": "ocasión",
    "questionDetails": "Hemos tenido ocasión de aumentar.",
    "answer": "occasion",
    "answerDetails": "We had occasion to raise it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2440,
    "question": "sacaron",
    "questionDetails": "Ellos me sacaron de mi casa.",
    "answer": "took",
    "answerDetails": "They took me from my house."
  },
  {
    "id": 2441,
    "question": "techo",
    "questionDetails": "La lluvia lo despertó, martilleando en el techo.",
    "answer": "roof",
    "answerDetails": "The rain woke him, hammering on the roof."
  },
  {
    "id": 2442,
    "question": "plato",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuántas veces te he dicho que quites tu plato de la mesa cuando termines?",
    "answer": "dish, plate, platter",
    "answerDetails": "How many times have I told you to remove your dish from the table when you’ve finished?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2443,
    "question": "profundo",
    "questionDetails": "La empresa busca contratar a alguien con conocimiento profundo de la soldadura.",
    "answer": "thorough, intense",
    "answerDetails": "The company seeks to hire someone with a thorough knowledge of welding."
  },
  {
    "id": 2444,
    "question": "abro",
    "questionDetails": "Abro con un dólar.",
    "answer": "open",
    "answerDetails": "Open for a buck."
  },
  {
    "id": 2445,
    "question": "imágenes",
    "questionDetails": "La cámara en realidad produce imágenes increíbles.",
    "answer": "imagery",
    "answerDetails": "This camera actually produces incredible imagery."
  },
  {
    "id": 2446,
    "question": "olor",
    "questionDetails": "27 gatos vivieron allí-se puede imaginar el olor!.",
    "answer": "smell, scent",
    "answerDetails": "27 cats lived there—you can imagine the smell!."
  },
  {
    "id": 2447,
    "question": "trabajado",
    "questionDetails": "Ya has trabajado bastante por hoy.",
    "answer": "worked, labored",
    "answerDetails": "I worked you enough for one day."
  },
  {
    "id": 2448,
    "question": "traía",
    "questionDetails": "Los traía aquí constantemente.",
    "answer": "brought",
    "answerDetails": "Brought them in here all the time."
  },
  {
    "id": 2449,
    "question": "acabado",
    "questionDetails": "El acabado del escritorio de tu abuelo quedó muy bien.",
    "answer": "finish",
    "answerDetails": "The finish on your grandfather’s desk came out really well."
  },
  {
    "id": 2450,
    "question": "cincuenta",
    "answer": "fifties"
  },
  {
    "id": 2451,
    "question": "original",
    "questionDetails": "El filme original tenía otro nombre.",
    "answer": "original",
    "answerDetails": "The original was a different name."
  },
  {
    "id": 2452,
    "question": "mejorar",
    "questionDetails": "Esfuerzos para mejorar las relaciones entre los países.",
    "answer": "improve",
    "answerDetails": "Efforts to improve relations between the countries."
  },
  {
    "id": 2453,
    "question": "entré",
    "questionDetails": "Simplemente entré a un concesionario y lo compré.",
    "answer": "walked",
    "answerDetails": "Just walked onto a lot and bought it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2454,
    "question": "llevé",
    "questionDetails": "Me llevé buenas palizas.",
    "answer": "took",
    "answerDetails": "I took some massive beatings there."
  },
  {
    "id": 2455,
    "question": "decías",
    "questionDetails": "En cuanto a lo que decías de tener hijos.",
    "answer": "said, kept saying",
    "answerDetails": "What you said about having children."
  },
  {
    "id": 2456,
    "question": "fila",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestros asientos están en la fila doce.",
    "answer": "row, line, rank",
    "answerDetails": "Our seats are in row 12."
  },
  {
    "id": 2457,
    "question": "intenta",
    "questionDetails": "Pobrecita Sheila. Intenta ingresar al maratón todos los años, pero nunca gana la lotería.",
    "answer": "she tries",
    "answerDetails": "Poor Sheila. She tries to get into the marathon every year, but never wins the lottery."
  },
  {
    "id": 2458,
    "question": "aquellos",
    "questionDetails": "Los mejores amigos son aquellos que están siempre ahí para tí.",
    "answer": "ones",
    "answerDetails": "The best friends are the ones who are always there for you."
  },
  {
    "id": 2459,
    "question": "distintos",
    "questionDetails": "La policía allanó una bodega para detener a los distintos miembros de una pandilla local.",
    "answer": "various",
    "answerDetails": "The police raided a warehouse in order to arrest the various members of a local gang."
  },
  {
    "id": 2460,
    "question": "video",
    "questionDetails": "El video muestra que el padre intentó detenerlo.",
    "answer": "video, tape",
    "answerDetails": "The video shows the father tried to stop it."
  },
  {
    "id": 2461,
    "question": "oíste",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que me oíste llamarte pero escogiste ignorarme.",
    "answer": "you heard, did you hear",
    "answerDetails": "I know you heard me calling you, but you chose to ignore me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2462,
    "question": "perra",
    "questionDetails": "Esa perra está tras mi marido.",
    "answer": "skank",
    "answerDetails": "That skank is after my man."
  },
  {
    "id": 2463,
    "question": "política",
    "questionDetails": "Nos oponemos a la política del gobierno de repatriar a niños inmigrantes a su país de orígen.",
    "answer": "policy",
    "answerDetails": "We oppose the government’s policy of sending migrant children back to their country of origin."
  },
  {
    "id": 2464,
    "question": "sexo",
    "questionDetails": "Usar el sexo como una escapatoria.",
    "answer": "sex, gender, laid",
    "answerDetails": "Using sex as an escape."
  },
  {
    "id": 2465,
    "question": "relájate",
    "questionDetails": "Ahora, relájate y sonríe.",
    "answer": "relax, chill out, chillax",
    "answerDetails": "Now relax and smile."
  },
  {
    "id": 2466,
    "question": "redes",
    "questionDetails": "Las redes sociales han estado siempre ahí.",
    "answer": "networks",
    "answerDetails": "Social networks have always been there."
  },
  {
    "id": 2467,
    "question": "horror",
    "questionDetails": "Me senté con horror congelado durante un minuto o dos.",
    "answer": "horror",
    "answerDetails": "I sat frozen with horror for a minute or two."
  },
  {
    "id": 2468,
    "question": "echando",
    "questionDetails": "Mira toda la culpa que te esta echando encima.",
    "answer": "throwing, casting, pouring",
    "answerDetails": "Look at the guilt he’s throwing your way."
  },
  {
    "id": 2469,
    "question": "metiste",
    "questionDetails": "Te metiste con mi lista.",
    "answer": "messed, get",
    "answerDetails": "You messed with my list item."
  },
  {
    "id": 2470,
    "question": "paseo",
    "questionDetails": "Si usted está en su y tiene que hacer el paseo temido de la vergüenza de casa, el acero usted mismo.",
    "answer": "walk, stroll, drive",
    "answerDetails": "If you’re at his and have to make the dreaded walk of shame home, steel yourself."
  },
  {
    "id": 2471,
    "question": "macho",
    "questionDetails": "Los pingüinos machos les dan guijarros a sus compañeras como regalos.",
    "answer": "male",
    "answerDetails": "Male Penguins give pebbles to their mates as gifts."
  },
  {
    "id": 2472,
    "question": "salvó",
    "questionDetails": "Ella dijo que le salvó la vida.",
    "answer": "saved, spared",
    "answerDetails": "She says you saved her life."
  },
  {
    "id": 2473,
    "question": "vivos",
    "questionDetails": "Flores eran para los vivos.",
    "answer": "living",
    "answerDetails": "Flowers were for the living."
  },
  {
    "id": 2474,
    "question": "pensó",
    "answer": "Thought"
  },
  {
    "id": 2475,
    "question": "metes",
    "questionDetails": "Te metes con el, y me respondes a mi.",
    "answer": "mess, get, tuck",
    "answerDetails": "You mess with him, you answer to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2476,
    "question": "pudieron",
    "questionDetails": "Hicieron todo lo que pudieron.",
    "answer": "could",
    "answerDetails": "They did everything they could do."
  },
  {
    "id": 2477,
    "question": "reloj",
    "questionDetails": "Adelantar/atrasar el reloj.",
    "answer": "clock, watch",
    "answerDetails": "To put the clock forward/back."
  },
  {
    "id": 2478,
    "question": "acceso",
    "questionDetails": "Nos negaron el acceso a nuestro nieto.",
    "answer": "access",
    "answerDetails": "We were denied access to our grandson."
  },
  {
    "id": 2479,
    "question": "registro",
    "questionDetails": "Bob trabaja en la sección inmobiliaria del registro.",
    "answer": "registry, log, register",
    "answerDetails": "Bob works in the property section of the registry."
  },
  {
    "id": 2480,
    "question": "copia",
    "questionDetails": "Puedo darte una copia de todos mis registros de pagos.",
    "answer": "copy",
    "answerDetails": "I can get you a copy of my payroll records."
  },
  {
    "id": 2481,
    "question": "trajeron",
    "questionDetails": "Invitamos a los vecinos a cenar. Ellos trajeron las bebidas y nosotros cocinamos.",
    "answer": "they brought",
    "answerDetails": "We invited the neighbors over for dinner. They brought the drinks and we cooked."
  },
  {
    "id": 2482,
    "question": "bailando",
    "questionDetails": "Ha comenzado la música y ahora estarán bailando.",
    "answer": "dancing, dancin’",
    "answerDetails": "The music has started and now they’ll be dancing."
  },
  {
    "id": 2483,
    "question": "impresión",
    "questionDetails": "Tener la impresión de que ….",
    "answer": "impression",
    "answerDetails": "To be under the impression that…."
  },
  {
    "id": 2484,
    "question": "buscas",
    "questionDetails": "Y de esa forma, ganarás el apoyo que buscas.",
    "answer": "seek, want",
    "answerDetails": "And by such, gain the favor you seek."
  },
  {
    "id": 2485,
    "question": "estarás",
    "questionDetails": "Supongo que no estarás bailando con las estrellas.",
    "answer": "be",
    "answerDetails": "Guess you won’t be dancing with the stars."
  },
  {
    "id": 2486,
    "question": "favorito",
    "questionDetails": "Los favoritos te ayudan a guardar sitios web a los que quieres regresar más tarde.",
    "answer": "bookmark",
    "answerDetails": "Bookmarks allow you to save Web sites that you want to come back to later."
  },
  {
    "id": 2487,
    "question": "entrado",
    "questionDetails": "No digas que hemos entrado.",
    "answer": "entered, stepped",
    "answerDetails": "Do not say that we have entered."
  },
  {
    "id": 2488,
    "question": "cerrada",
    "questionDetails": "Mentira, la puerta estaba cerrada.",
    "answer": "closed, shut, locked",
    "answerDetails": "The door was closed."
  },
  {
    "id": 2489,
    "question": "pendejo",
    "questionDetails": "Deberías ser un pendejo.",
    "answer": "prick",
    "answerDetails": "You should be a prick."
  },
  {
    "id": 2490,
    "question": "siéntese",
    "questionDetails": "Acerque esa silla y siéntese aquí a mi lado.",
    "answer": "sit down, sit",
    "answerDetails": "Pull up that chair and sit down next to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 2491,
    "question": "drogas",
    "questionDetails": "No compres las drogas.",
    "answer": "drugs, dope",
    "answerDetails": "Do not buy the drugs."
  },
  {
    "id": 2492,
    "question": "armar",
    "questionDetails": "Se armaron con espadas y escudos para la batalla.",
    "answer": "arm",
    "answerDetails": "They armed themselves with swords and shields for the battle."
  },
  {
    "id": 2493,
    "question": "show",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos un trato para un show.",
    "answer": "act",
    "answerDetails": "We got a deal for one act."
  },
  {
    "id": 2494,
    "question": "abogados",
    "questionDetails": "Y usted sabe el problema con los abogados.",
    "answer": "lawyers, attorneys, solicitors",
    "answerDetails": "And you know the problem with the lawyers."
  },
  {
    "id": 2495,
    "question": "pendientes",
    "questionDetails": "Los pendientes con corazones de diamante.",
    "answer": "earrings, pending, slopes",
    "answerDetails": "The earrings with the diamond hearts."
  },
  {
    "id": 2496,
    "question": "maté",
    "questionDetails": "Ya te maté una vez.",
    "answer": "killed",
    "answerDetails": "I killed you once."
  },
  {
    "id": 2497,
    "question": "maleta",
    "questionDetails": "Por causa de la maleta.",
    "answer": "suitcase",
    "answerDetails": "Because of the suitcase."
  },
  {
    "id": 2498,
    "question": "cobrar",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuánto me vas a cobrar por la comida?",
    "answer": "charge, collect, levy",
    "answerDetails": "How much are you going to charge for the meal?"
  },
  {
    "id": 2499,
    "question": "caballo",
    "questionDetails": "Puedo estar allá con mi caballo.",
    "answer": "horse",
    "answerDetails": "He could have been out there with my horse."
  },
  {
    "id": 2500,
    "question": "dispuesta",
    "questionDetails": "Ella estaba dispuesta a tomar de esa manera.",
    "answer": "willing, arranged, ready",
    "answerDetails": "She was willing to take it that way."
  }
]
